《惊声尖叫》
- Hello? -  Hello.
- 喂 -  喂
- Yes? - Who is this?
- 你找？ - 你是谁？
- Who you trying to reach? - What number is this?
- 你想找谁？ - 这个电话号码是？
- What number are you trying to reach? - I don't know.
- 你想打的是哪个电话号码？ - 我不知道
- I think you have the wrong number. - Do I?
- 我想你打错了 - 是吗？
It happens. Take it easy.
不要紧，没关系的
- Hello! - I'm sorry. I guess I dialed the wrong number.
- 喂！ - 对不起，我猜我刚才打错了
- So, why'd you dial it again? - To apologize.
- 那你为什么还要再打进来？ - 来道歉
- You're forgiven. Bye, now. - Wait, wait! Don't hang up.
- 我原谅你了，再见 - 等等，别挂
- What? - I wanna talk to you for a second.
- 为什么？ - 我想跟你谈一小会儿
They've got 900-numbers for that. See ya.
你想聊天的话，可以去打900收费电话 再见
- Hello. - Why don't you want to talk to me?
- 喂 - 你为什么不想和我聊一聊？
Who is this?
你是谁呀？
You tell me your name, I'll tell you mine.
你先告诉我你的名字，我再说我的
I don't think so.
不行
- What's that noise? - Popcorn.
- 那是什么声音？ - 爆米花
- You're making popcorn? - Uh-huh.
- 你在做爆米花？ - 是的
I only eat popcorn at the movies.
我只在看电影时才吃爆米花
- Well, I'm getting ready to watch a video. - Really? What?
- 我准备看录像了 - 是吗？什么录像？
Oh, just some scary movie.
一个恐怖电影
- You like scary movies? - Uh-huh.
- 你喜欢恐怖电影吗？ - 是呀
What's your favorite scary movie?
你最喜欢看哪部恐怖电影？
- Uh, I don't know. - You have to have a favorite.
- 我不知道 - 你肯定有一个最喜欢看的
What comes to mind?
想起来了吗？
Um... "Halloween."
嗯...《鬼节》吧
You know, the one with the guy in the white mask...
你知道，那个戴白面具的家伙...
who walks around and stalks baby-sitters.
他四处寻找猎物， 最后盯上了那个临时保姆
-  Yeah. - What's yours?
-  是吗 - 那你最喜欢的是什么？
- Guess. - Um... "Nightmare on Elm Street."
- 你猜 - 嗯...<猛鬼街>
Is that the one where the guy had knives for fingers?
是不是有个家伙的手指是刀子？
- Yeah, Freddy Krueger. - Freddy, that's right.
- 是的，弗莱迪·克鲁戈 - 弗莱迪，对，就是他
I liked that movie. It was scary.
我喜欢那个电影，很恐怖
Yeah, the first one was, but the rest sucked.
是呀，第一部很恐怖， 但是其他的都很差
So, you got a boyfriend?
那你有男朋友吗？
Why? You wanna ask me out on a date?
怎么了？你想和我约会吗？
Maybe. Do you have a boyfriend?
很可能你有还是没有男朋友？
- Mm... no. - You never told me your name.
- 嗯...没有 - 你还没有告诉我你的名字呢
Why do you want to know my name?
你为什么想知道我的名字？
'Cause I wanna know who I'm looking at.
因为我想知道我现在正在看谁
- What did you say? - I wanna know who I'm talking to.
- 你说什么？ - 我想知道我在和谁说话
That's not what you said.
刚才你不是这样说的
What do you think I said?
那你说我刚才说的是什么？
What?
什么？
Hello?
喂？
Look, I gotta go.
注意，我要挂线了
Wait! I thought we were gonna go out.
等等！我们不是说要出去约会的吗
Uh, nah, I don't think so.
我不会去的
Don't hang up on me!
不要挂断！
Shit.
该死
- Yes? - I told you not to hang up on me.
- 干什么？ - 我叫你别挂线的
- What do you want? - To talk.
- 你究竟想干什么？ - 想聊聊
Well, dial someone else, okay?
你打给别人去好不好？
- Listen, asshole! - No, you listen, you little bitch!
- 听着，混蛋！ - 你给我听着，你这个小婊子！
You hang up on me again,
你又把我的电话挂断了
I'll cut you like a fish, understand?
我要把你象鱼一样宰了，知道吗？
Yeah.
好不好啊
Is this some kind of joke?
这是开玩笑吗？
More of a game, really.
不，实际上更像一种游戏
Can you handle that...
你应付得了吗？
blondie?
金发女郎？
Can you see me?
你能看得见我吗？
Listen, I am two seconds away from calling the police.
听着，我马上就要叫警察了
They'd never make it in time. We're out in the middle of nowhere.
叫他们已经来不及了， 他们离这儿太远了
What do you want?
你究竟想干什么？
To see what your insides look like.
想看看你身体内部究竟是什么样的
Who's there? Who's there?
是谁？谁在那儿？
I'm calling the police.
我在打电话
You should never say, "Who's there?"
你不该问“谁在那儿”
Don't you watch scary movies? It's a death wish.
你没看过恐怖电影吗？ 那是求死愿望
You might as well just come out here to investigate a strange noise or somethin'.
你也应该过来看看这儿 是不是有什么怪声的
Look, you've had your fun now...
听着，你现在已经玩够了
- so I think you better just leave or else. - Or else what?
- 你最好马上离开，否则 - 否则什么？
Or else my boyfriend'll be here any second, and he'll be pissed when he finds out.
我男朋友快来这儿了， 他知道了会大发雷霆的
I thought you didn't have a boyfriend.
我认为你没有男朋友
I lied! I do have a boyfriend, and he'll be here any second...
我撒谎了！ 我确实有男朋友，并且会随时来这儿
- so your ass better be gone. - Sure.
- 所以你这头蠢驴最好赶快滚 - 好呀
I swear.
我说真的
He's big, and he plays football
他很壮，是个橄榄球队员
and he'll kick the shit out of you!
他会把你的屎都打出来的！
I'm getting scared. I'm shaking in my boots.
我好害怕哟，我的腿在发抖
So you better just leave.
所以你最好赶紧走
His name wouldn't be...
他不是叫...
Steve, would it?
斯蒂夫吗，对不对？
How do you know his name?
你怎么知道他的名字的？
Turn on the patio lights... again.
你再打开院子里的灯...
Oh, God!
天哪！
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
如果我是你， 我不会那样干的
Where are you?
你在哪儿？
- Guess. - Please don't hurt him.
- 猜猜看 - 请不要伤害我
- That all depends on you. - Why are you doing this?
- 那要看你了 - 你为什么要这样做？
- I wanna play a game. - No.
- 我想玩一个游戏 - 不
- Then he dies right now! - No! No!
- 那他马上就会死！ - 不！不！
Which is it? Which is it?
到底玩不玩？ 到底玩不玩？
Wha... What kind of game?
什...什么样的游戏？
Turn off the light. You'll see what kind of game.
关上灯， 你会看到是什么样的游戏的
Just do it!
快！
Casey! No! No!
凯西！不要！不要！
No! Casey!
别！凯西！
Here's how we play.
我们开始玩吧
I ask a question. If you get it right, Steve lives.
我问问题， 如果你答对了，斯蒂夫便可以不死
- Please don't do this. - Come on. It'll be fun.
- 请不要这样了 - 来吧，很好玩的
- Please... - It's an easy category.
- 求求你... - 这是简单的那类问题
- Please... - Movie trivia.
- 求求你... - 有关电影的细节问题
- I'll even give you a warm-up question. - Don't do this. I can't.
- 先给你来个热身的问题吧 - 请别这样，我不会
- Name the killer in "Halloween." - No.
- 说出《鬼节》中杀手的名字 - 不
Come on! It's your favorite scary movie, remember?
来吧！ 这是你最喜欢的恐怖电影，还记得吗？
He had a white mask; he stalked the baby-sitters.
他有一个白色的面具 他盯上了那个保姆
I don't know.
我不知道
- Come on. Yes, you do. - No, please.
- 得了，你知道的 - 请别玩了
- What's his name? - I can't think.
- 他叫什么名字？ - 我现在不能思考
Steve's counting on you.
斯蒂夫的性命就靠你了
Michael... Michael, Michael.
麦克尔...麦克尔，麦克尔
Yes! Very good.
对！非常好
Now for the real question.
现在来开始正式的问题
- No! - But you're doing so well.
- 不要！ - 刚才你玩得很不错嘛
We can't stop now.
我们现在不能停下来
Please stop! Leave us alone!
请不要这样！放过我们吧！
Answer the question. Same category.
来回答另一个同类型的问题
Oh, please stop.
求求你停下来
Name the killer in "Friday the 13th."
说出《十三号星期五》中杀手的名字
Jason! Jason, Jason!
贾森！贾森，贾森！
I'm sorry. That's the wrong answer.
很抱歉，你答错了
No, it's not! No, it's not. It was Jason.
不，我没错！不，我没错！就是贾森
Afraid not. No way.
恐怕不是的，你错了
Listen, it was Jason! I saw that movie 20 goddamn times!
听着，就是贾森！ 那个电影我他妈看过20遍了！
Then you should know Jason's mother,
那你应该知道贾森的老娘
Mrs. Voorhees, was the original killer.
沃希斯太太，是最初的杀手
Jason didn't show up until the sequel.
贾森最后才出场
I'm afraid that was a wrong answer.
恐怕你答错了
You tricked me.
你在玩我
Lucky for you there's a bonus round.
你很幸运，我再给你一个机会
But poor Steve. I'm afraid he's out!
但是可怜的史蒂夫，我想他完蛋了！
Hey, we're not finished yet.
嗨，我们还没完哪
Final question. Are you ready?
最后一个问题你准备好了吗？
Please, please, leave me alone.
求求你放过我
Answer the question, and I will.
答对了，我就放过你
What door am I at?
我在哪个门外？
- What? - There are two main doors to your house.
- 什么？ - 这个房子有两个大门
The front door, the patio doors.
前门和院子里的门
If you answer correctly, you live.
你答对了，便不会死
Very simple.
很简单
Don't do this. I can't; I won't.
不要这样做 我不能回答！我不会回答！
Your call.
注意了
Aah!
啊哈！
Did you water over here today?
你今天在这儿浇水了吗？
- It was just that water from the rain. - They look great, don't they?
- 那只是雨水 - 它们看起来很不错，对不？
Don't they smell strong?
闻起来不也很香吗？
I told you you could send it back.
我跟你说了可以把它们送回去了
Mom!
妈妈！
- Jesus! - What is it?
- 天哪！ - 这是什么？
Casey!
凯西！
Oh, G...
唉呀，天...
Casey. Casey.
凯西！凯西！
Casey!
凯西！
- Where is she? - Call the police!
- 她在哪？ - 快报警！
Casey!
凯西！
Casey, are you upstairs?
凯西，你在楼上吗？
Oh, my God. Casey, baby?
噢，老天！凯西，宝贝？
-  Casey? -  She's here.
-  凯西？ -  她在这里
- Mom. -  Oh, my God, I can hear her.
- 妈妈 -  噢，天哪！ 我能听见她声音
- s Mom. - Where is she?
- 妈妈 - 她在哪？
Oh, my God! I can hear her.
噢，天哪！我能听见她声音
Hey!
嗨！
Get in the car. Drive down to the MacKenzies'.
快进车，到麦肯齐家去
- No. No, not my daughter. - Just go.
- 不，不，那不是我女儿！ - 快走
- Not my daughter. - Call the police.
- 不是我女儿！ - 去报警
It's just me.
是我
- Billy, what are you doing here? - Sorry, don't hate me.
- 比利，你来这儿干什么？ - 抱歉，不要怪我
- You sleep in that? - Yes, I sleep in this.
- 这是你的卧室？ - 是的
My dad is in the other room. You can't be in here.
我爸就在隔壁，你不能在这儿
I'll just stay a sec.
我只呆一会儿
No...You gotta go. Go, go, go.
啊...你快走吧快！快！快！
What's going on in there?
发生什么事了？
- Are you okay? - Can you knock?
- 你没事吧？ - 你不会先敲门吗？
- I heard screaming. - No, you didn't.
- 我听见尖叫声 - 不，我没有
No?
没有？
Oh, well. I'm hitting the sack.
哦，是吗？我正准备睡觉
My flight leaves first thing in the morning.
我明天一早的飞机
Now, the expo runs all weekend, so I won't be back 'til Sunday.
整个周末都有展览， 我起码要到星期天才回来
- There's cash on the table, and I'm staying at... - The Hilton.
- 桌上有钱，我会住在... - 希尔顿
- Out at the airport, so call if... - I need anything.
- 就在机超打电话给我，如果... - 有事的话
I could've sworn I heard screaming.
我肯定我听见了尖叫声
Have a good trip, okay?
祝旅途愉快！爸爸
Sleep tight, sweetie.
好好睡，宝贝
Oh... close call.
噢...差一点被发现
Billy, what're you doing here?
比利，你到这儿干什么？
It occurred to me that...
我刚想到...
I've never snuck through your bedroom window.
我还没有试过从你的卧室窗户进来
Shh, shh, shh.
嘘...嘘...嘘
Great idea, now that it's out of your system.
你现在进来了，那就赶紧走吧
I was home watching television.
我刚刚在家看电视
"The," uh, "The Exorcist" was on.
正在放那个，嗯...那个《驱魔人》
- It got me thinking of you. - It did?
- 它使我想起了你 - 是吗？
Yeah, it was edited for TV.
是的，不过那是电视版的
You know, all the good stuff was cut out.
你知道，好东西都被剪掉了
And it got me thinking of us...
也使我想起了我们...
how two years ago we started off hot and heavy.
两年那充满激情的开始
Nice solid R-rating on our way to an NC-17.
关系就像R级电影，眼看我们就可以像NC-17级了
And now... things have changed and...
可是现在...一切都变了
lately we're just sort of edited for television.
现在我们的关系就像剪辑过的电视版
Oh, so you thought you would climb in my window...
那你觉得就应该爬进我的窗户来...
- and we'd have a little raw footage? -  No.
- 并且跟我表演一点被剪掉的镜头？ -  不
No, I wouldn't dream of breaking your underwear rule.
不，我不会突破你的内衣底线的
I just thought maybe we could do a little on-top-of-the-clothes stuff.
我在想，我们可以穿着衣服来做
- Okay. - Yeah?
- 好吧 - 真的？
Yeah.
是的
Hey.
嗨
Okay. Okay, okay. Time is up, stud-muffin.
好了，好了，时间到了，性感猛男
God, you see what you do to me?
天哪，你看你怎么对待我
You know what my dad'll do to you?
你知道我爸会怎样对你吗？
Yeah.
好吧
- I'm going. - Okay.
- 我走了 - 好吧
You know, I... I appreciate the romantic gesture.
你知道， 我...我很感激你这种浪漫情调
Hey, about the, uh, the sex stuff?
嗨，关于那个性方面的事，
I'm not trying to rush you at all.
我根本不是想催促你
I was only half serious.
我只是半开玩笑的
Okay.
好的
Hey, Billy.
嗨，比利
Would you settle for a PG-13 relationship?
我们来个PG-13级的关系怎样？
What's that?
那是什么样的？
My God. You're just a tease.
哼，别取笑我了
Thirty-five
三十五
Situation under control.
局势已被控制
Roger, dispatch.
罗杰，你去
There's blood found? All right.
发现了血？好的
are doing drugs they buy in the classrooms...
在教室里吸毒...
and that they are involved in the occult.
并涉及那件神秘的事件
Occult?
神秘的事？
Woodsboro, California, was devastated last night...
加州伍兹士堡昨晚被震惊了...
when two young teenagers were found brutally murdered.
两名十几岁的学生被残忍地谋杀
Authorities have yet to issue a statement...
警方至今未作任何说明
but our sources tell us that no arrest has been made...
但消息来源说未有人被捕...
- and the murderer could strike again. - Do you believe this shit?
- 凶手可能再次作案 - 你相信这件事吗？
- Damn! What is going on? - You don't know?
- 发生了什么事？ - 你还不知道？
Casey Becker and Steve Orth were killed last night.
凯西·贝克尔和史蒂夫·厄斯 昨晚被杀了
What? No way.
什么？不会吧！
And we're not just talking killed; we're talking splatter-movie killed.
不止是被杀，而且还是血腥的谋杀
Ripped open from end to end.
从头到脚都被割开了
Casey Becker, she sits next to me in English.
凯西·贝克尔？ 她上英语课时坐在我的旁边呀
Not anymore. It's so sad.
以后不会了 真是太不幸了
Her mom and dad, they found her hanging from a tree...
她的爸爸和妈妈 发现她吊在一棵树下...
- her insides on the outside. - Oh, my God!
- 她的内脏露在外面 - 天哪！
Do they know who did it?
他们知道谁是凶手吗？
Fucking clueless. They're interrogating the entire school.
一点线索都没有 他们正对校内所有人问话
Teachers, students, janitors.
教师，学生，工友等
They think it's school-related?
他们认为跟校内的人有关？
They don't know.
他们不知道
Dewey was saying this is the worst crime they've seen in years.
杜威说他们已经 多年没见过这么恶性的案件
Even worse than
更糟的是
Well... it's bad.
是啊...很糟糕
-  Here you go, Mrs. Tate. - Thank you, James.
-  给您，泰特太太 - 谢谢你，詹姆士
Sidney.
希德内
It would appear to be your turn.
到你了
- Who's up next? - Uh, Sidney Prescott.
- 谁是下一个？ - 哦，希德内·普里斯科特
She was daughter of, uh...
她是...的女儿，唉...
- Sidney, how you feelin'? - Fine.
- 希德内，感觉怎么样？ - 还好
Hi, Sidney.
嗨，希德内
Sheriff Burke, Dewey.
治安官伯克，杜威
Uh, that's Deputy Riley today, Sid.
哦，希德内，那是副警长莱利
-  How is everything? - Good.
-  你好吗？ - 好
And your dad? How's he doin'?
你父亲怎样？他还好吗？
We're fine. Thanks.
我们很好谢谢
We're gonna keep this very brief, Sidney.
希德内， 我们不会耽误你太长时间的
The police just want to ask you a few questions. You okay?
警察只想问你几个问题，可以吗？
Mm-hmm.
好的
Sidney, were you very close to Casey Becker?
希德内， 你和凯西·贝克尔的关系很好吗？
Remember, your principal loves you, and I want you to be safe.
记赚你们的校长是爱你们的，我希望你们每个人都平安
All students are encouraged to return home promptly from school grounds.
所有的学生请从学校立即回家
Avoid strangers; walk in twos and threes.
请结伴回家，不要跟陌生人接触
What kind of questions did they ask you, Sidney?
希德内， 他们问你什么问题了？
They asked if I knew Casey.
他们问我是否认识凯西
They asked me that too.
他们也问我同样的问题
- Hey, did they ask if you like to hunt? - Yeah, they did.
- 嗨，他们有问你喜欢打猎吗？ - 是呀他们问了
Did they ask you?
他们问了你没有？
Why would they ask you if you liked to hunt?
他们为什么要问你这个问题？
'Cause their bodies were gutted.
因为被害者的尸体都被开膛了
- Thank you, Randy. - They didn't ask me if I like to hunt.
- 谢谢，兰迪 - 他们没有问我是否喜欢打猎
- 'Cause there's no way a girl could've killed 'em. - That is so sexist.
- 因为凶手不可能是个女孩 - 大男子主义
The killer could easily be female. "Basic Instinct."
凶手有可能是女性 看过《本能》吗？
That was an ice pick. Not exactly the same thing.
那是用的破冰锤， 跟这不是一码事
Yeah, Casey and Steve were completely hollowed out.
是呀！ 凯西和史蒂夫的内脏全被掏出来了
And the fact is, it takes a man to do something like that.
事实是，只有男的才干得出来
Or a man's mentality.
或是男人型的女人
How do you... gut someone?
你知道怎样... 才能把人的内脏挖出来？
You take a knife, and you slit 'em from the groin to sternum.
用一把刀，从腹股沟一直割到胸骨
Hey, it's called tact, you fuck rag.
嗨，别说了， 你这个追求感官刺激的家伙
Hey, Stu, didn't you used to date Casey?
嘿，斯图， 你没有和凯西约会过吗？
Yeah, for like two seconds.
有过，很短
Before she dumped him for Steve.
在她为了史蒂夫 而甩了他之前
I thought you dumped her for me.
我还以为你是为我 而把她踹了呢
I did. He's full of shit.
当然是呀！别听他胡说
And are the police aware that you dated the victim?
警察知道你和被害者有过约会吗？
Hey, what're you saying? That I killed her?
嘿，你说什么？我杀了他？
It would certainly improve your high school "Q."
那绝对会提高你 高中生活的质量
- Stu was with me last night, okay? - Yeah, I was.
- 斯图昨晚和我在一起，好不好？ - 是，确实是
Was that before or after he sliced and diced?
那是在杀人之前还是在之后？
Fuck you, nutcase. Where were you last night?
去你的，你这个疯子 昨晚你又在哪儿？
Working, thank you.
在工作
At the video store? I thought they fired your ass.
还在那个音像店？ 我还以为他们把你炒了呢
Twice.
炒过两次
- I didn't kill anybody. - Nobody said you did.
- 我没有杀任何人 - 没有人说你杀了人
Thanks, buddy.
谢谢，老兄
Besides, it takes a man to do something like that.
再说， 只有男人才下得了那样的手
- I'm gonna gut your ass in a second, kid. - Tell me something.
- 我马上就把你的屁股割下来，小子 - 告诉我，
Did you really put her liver in the mailbox?
你是不是真的把她的肝放进了信箱？
'Cause I heard that they found her liver in the mailbox next to her spleen and pancreas.
我听说他们在信箱里 找到了她的肝，脾和胰
You goon! Fuck! I'm trying to eat here.
你这个混蛋！我还想在这儿吃东西呢
She's getting mad, all right?
她已经受不了了，对吧？
You better "liver" alone.
你最好"肝"远一点
"Liver" alone!
“肝”远一点！
"Liv..." Ow! "Liver, Liver". It was a joke.
“肝...”，噢！ “肝、肝、肝”，开个玩笑而已
See you, Sidney. I'll talk to you tomorrow, Sid.
再见，希德内 明天见，希德内
So, you're sure I can stay over, 'cause my dad won't be back 'til Sunday.
那，你确信我可以过夜吗？ 我爸爸到星期天才会回来
No problem. I'll pick you up after practice.
没问题 我锻炼完后就来接你
You okay?
你没事吧？
Uh-huh. It's just...
嗯...嗯，只是...
you know, the police and the reporters...
你知道，警察和那些记者们...
it's like deja vu all over again.
对我而言有一种似曾相识的感觉
I'll be there by 7:00. I promise.
我7点钟一定到你那儿，我发誓
- Thanks, Tatum. - Later.
- 谢谢，塔特姆 - 过会儿见
The bodies of 17-year-old Casey Becker...
17岁的凯西·贝克尔...
and her 18-year-old boyfriend, Steven Orth...
和她的18岁男友 史蒂夫·厄斯的尸体，
were discovered late last night by the girl's parents...
昨天晚上被女孩的父母发现...
The Woodsboro double murder case.
伍兹士堡双重谋杀案
Authorities are baffled by the lack of clues and the savage...
警方正为缺少线索而为难， 而残暴的凶手...
The town's in shock, and no one can quite believe what has happened here...
惨案震惊了全镇，没有人愿相信这里发生的惨案
although this is not the first time this small community...
虽然这不是伍兹士堡小镇首次...
of Woodsboro has endured such tragedy.
经历这种惨剧
Only a year ago Maureen Prescott, wife and mother...
仅仅在一年前，毛里恩·普里斯科特，一位妻子兼母亲
was found raped and murdered not far from this peaceful town square.
被强奸并杀害在这个 安宁的小镇广场不远处
- Hello? - Practice ran late. I'm on my way, okay?
- 喂？ - 锻炼得太晚了我就来，好吗？
It's past 7:00.
七点过了
Don't worry. Casey and Steve didn't bite it 'til way after 10:00.
别担心, 凯西和史蒂夫都是十点后才遇害的
Oh. Oh, that's comforting.
哦，哦，这令我放心多了
I'm gonna swing by the video store.
我要去一趟音像店
I was thinkin' Tom Cruise, "All The Right Moves."
我在考虑租汤姆·克鲁斯 的《步步登天》
If you pause it just right, you can see his penis.
如果你在适当的地方暂停下来， 你可以看见他的阳具
Whatever. Just hurry, okay?
不管怎样，你快点儿来，好吗？
Ta-ta, Sid.
那回头见，希德
- Tatum, just get in the car  -  Hello, Sidney.
- 塔特姆，快开车过来  -  你好，希德尼
Uh... hi, who is this?
嗯...嗨，你是谁？
You tell me.
你告诉我
Well, I-I have no idea.
唔...，我，我不知道
Scary night, isn't it?
恐怖的夜晚，是吧？
With the murders and all, it's like right out of a horror movie or something.
那些谋杀， 太像恐怖电影里的情节了
Randy, you gave yourself away.
兰迪，我知道是你了
Are you calling from work, 'cause Tatum's on her way over.
你是从工作的地方来电的吧，  塔特姆正往你那儿去
Do you like scary movies, Sidney?
你喜欢恐怖电影吗，希德内？
I like that thing you're doing with your voice, Randy. It's sexy.
我喜欢你这种语调，兰迪很性感
What's your favorite scary movie?
你最喜欢的恐怖电影是什么？
Oh, come on. You know I don't watch that shit.
噢，得了 你知道我不看那些垃圾的
- Why not? Too scared? - No. No.
- 为什么不？害怕？ - 不，不
It's just, what's the point? They're all the same.
只是，怎么说呢？ 它们看起来都一样
Some stupid killer stalking some big-breasted girl who can't act...
愚蠢的凶手总是猎杀 那些毫无反抗的大波妹
who's always running up the stairs when she should be going out the front door.
这些大波妹总是跑上楼， 而不懂应该从正门出去
- It's insulting. - Are you alone in the house?
- 这真是对观众的侮辱 - 你一个人在家吗？
Randy, that's so unoriginal. I'm disappointed in you.
兰迪，问得太没有创意了 真对你失望
Maybe that's because I'm not Randy.
也许那是因为我不是兰迪
So, who are you?
那，你是谁？
The question isn't "Who am I?"
你不应问“我是谁”
The question is "Where am I?"
而应问“我在哪儿”
S-S-So, where are you?
那，那...，你在哪儿？
Your front porch.
你家前门廊
Why would you be calling from my front porch?
你为什么要在那儿打电话？
That's the original part.
这个问题有创意
Oh, yeah?
噢，是吗？
Well, I call your bluff.
哼，我说你是个骗子
- So, where are you? - Right here.
- 你在哪儿？ - 就在这儿
- Can you see me right now? - Uh-huh.
- 你现在能看见我吗？ - 当然
Uh-huh, okay.
当然？好吧
What am I doin'? Huh?
我现在在干嘛？翱
Huh? What am I doin'? Hello!
哈哈？我在干嘛？ 喂！
Nice try, Randy.
演得不错，兰迪
Tell Tatum to hurry up, okay? Bye now.
叫塔特姆快点，好不？ 再见
If you hang up on me, you'll die just like your mother!
如果你挂断， 你就会像你妈一样死！
Do you wanna die, Sidney? Your mother sure didn't.
你想死吗，希德内？ 你妈是肯定不想的
Fuck you, you cretin!
去你的，杂种！
No!
不！
Shit!
靠！
Billy!
比利！
The door's locked. I heard screaming. You all right?
门锁上了我听到了尖叫声 你没事吧？
The killer's here. He's in the house.
杀手在这儿 他在这房子里
He's in the house. He's got a knife.
他在屋子里 他有刀
He's gone. He's gone.
他走了 他走了
It's all right.
没事了
What?
什么？
Sid, what?
希德内，怎么了？
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait. Wait, Sidney, wait!
喂，喂，等等，等等 等等，希德内，等等！
Wait, wait, wait, wait! What's going on?
等等，等等，等等，等等！ 怎么了？
Sidney, come back! Sidney!
希德内，回来！希德内！
Sorry! I found this. Come on!
对不起！我找到这个来吧！
All right, hold your hands together.
好了，并拢双手
Do you wish to give up your right to remain silent?
你想放弃保持沉默的权利吗？
I didn't do anything.
我没有干任何事
Do you wish to give up your right to speak to an attorney...
你想放弃和律师谈话的权力...
and have them present during questioning?
及讯问时律师可以在场的权力吗？
Ask her. She'll tell you.
问她，她会告诉你的
- I caught him, Sheriff. - Wait. Who is that?
- 我逮住他了，治安官 - 等等，他是谁？
- Billy Loomis. - Sheriff, Sheriff, call these guys off.
- 比利·卢米斯 - 治安官，治安官，放开我
I didn't do it. Sheriff, wait.
不是我 治安官，等等
Wait, listen. Call my dad.
等等，听着 打电话给我爸爸
Please, call him. He'll tell you. Call him.
求你了，打电话给我爸 他会告诉你的请打个电话
Sidney! Sidney!
希德内！希德内！
- How's she doing? - Sid's tougher than she looks.
- 她怎样？ - 希德内比看起来坚强
She'd have to be, all the shit she's been through.
她必须这样， 经历了这么多糟糕的事
-  Sid! - Well, we're seein' a lot of you today.
-  希德内！ - 是呀，今天我们又见到你了
You gonna be able to come down to the station and answer a few questions, Sid?
希德内，请跟我们到警局， 有些问题要问你
Oh, shit! Sidney!
艾该死！希德内！
God, Sid, I'm so sorry I was late. Are you all right?
天艾希德内，非常对不起， 我来晚了你没事吧？
Tatum, you can't be here. This is an official crime scene.
塔特姆，你不能在这儿， 这是犯罪现场
- It's okay. - Her dad's out of town. She's staying with us.
- 没关系 - 她爸爸出差了，她要住我们家
Does Mom know?
妈妈知道吗？
- Yes, doofus. - Let's get you out of here.
- 知道，猪头 - 我们走吧
-  She'll be okay. - Thanks.
-  她会没事的 - 谢谢
Oh, you won't believe this.
噢，你不会相信这的
Creepy, huh?
令人毛骨悚然，对吧？
- I'll be damned. - What?
- 我真该死 - 什么？
- Jesus! The camera, hurry! - My name isn't Jesus.
- 老天！快取摄像机！ - 我的名字不是老天
Sidney, is that you in there?
希德内，是你在里面吗？
Excuse me. Is that Sidney Prescott they took away?
对不起，请问他们带走的是 希德内·普里斯科特吗？
- I'm not talking to you. - What happened to her?
- 不告诉你 - 她怎么了？
- None of your damned business. - I heard something about a costume. Is that true?
- 不管你的屁事 - 我听说有一个面具，对不对？
Can you tell me anything?
你一点消息都不能告诉我吗？
Yeah, you're a real pain in the ass.
好艾，你是屁眼里的痔疮
Leave Sid alone.
别去烦希德内
Where's she goin'?
她去哪儿了？
- Look. Kenny? - Yeah?
- 听着，肯尼 - 什么？
I know that you're about 50 pounds overweight...
我知道你超重过50磅...
but when I say "hurry",
但当我说“快”时，
please interpret that as
请理解为
"move your fat, tub-of-lard ass now!"
“立即移动你这头 肥胖、笨拙的蠢驴的大屁股”
Did you find him?
找到他了吗？
You sure it was the Hilton?
确信在希尔顿饭店？
- At the airport. - He's not registered there.
- 机场那儿的 - 他没在那儿登记
Could he have stayed somewhere else?
他会在别的什么地方吗？
I don't know. I guess.
我想我不知道
Don't worry, Sid.
没关系，希德
We'll find him.
我们会找到他的
Dewey, they got that mask in.
杜威，他们把那个面具拿来了
I'll be right back.
我马上回来
Let me ask you this. What're you doin' with a cellular telephone, son?
我来问你，小子， 你拿着个手机干什么？
Everybody's got one, Sheriff.
治安官，每个人都有的
I didn't make those calls, I swear.
我发誓，不是我打的
Check the phone bill, for Christ's sake.
看在上帝的份上， 干嘛不去查查电话帐单？
Call Vital Phone Comp. They got the records of every number dialed.
打电话给威特尔电话公司， 他们有全部的通信记录
Thanks, Hank. We're on top of it.
谢谢，汉克斯 我们知道
What were you doing over at Sidney's house tonight?
你今晚跑到希德内家去干什么？
I wanted to see her, that's all.
我只是想见见她
And last night? Sidney said you crawled through her window last night too.
那昨晚呢？希德内说你 昨晚也爬进了她的窗户
You went out last night?
你昨晚出去了？
I was watching TV. I got bored. I decided to go for a ride.
我看电视看烦了， 就决定出去兜兜风
Did you happen to ride by Casey Becker's house?
你是否正好就兜到 凯西·贝克尔的家了？
No, I didn't. Sheriff, I didn't kill anybody!
没有，我没有，治安官 我没有杀任何人！
We're gonna have to hold you, son, 'til we get those phone records.
在那些电话记录来之前， 我们不能放你，小子
That's crazy.
这真荒唐
You know that? I didn't do it.
你知道的，不是我干的
Camera Two? Okay.
二号机？好的
Are there anymore doughnuts in there?
里面还有更多的面包圈吗？
- Move it, Kenny. - They're not lettin' anybody in.
- 快走，肯尼 - 他们不会让任何人进的
- I'm not just anyone. -  Bitch goddess.
- 我不是普通人 -  变态婊子
- Kenny, are we on? - Yeah, go.
- 肯尼，好了吗？ - 好了，开始
Hi, Gale Weathers reporting live from Woodsboro police station...
大家好，这是基尔·唯茨在伍兹士堡警察局的现场报道
where we hope to get a glimpse of Sidney Prescott.
我们希望能采访到 希德内·普里斯科特
Hey, watch it, lady.
嗨，注意，女士
Hey, watch the hand! Do you know who you're dealing with?
嗨，拿开你的手， 你知道我是谁吗？
Tell 'em. Come on, Dad. Tell 'em!
告诉他们 没事，爸爸告诉他们！
- He's waiting for the lawyer, Billy. - Sidney!
- 他正在等律师，比利 - 希德内！
Sidney, come on. You know me.
希德内，快点！ 你了解我
Sidney, look at me!
希德内，看看我
Come on!
快点！
Sid, we're gonna get you out of here, okay? Are you okay?
希德，我们离开这里吧，好吗？ 你没事吧？
They sell this costume at every five-and-dime in the state.
这种面具在每个廉价店里都有卖
There's no way to track the purchase.
不可能从这里找出线索
What about that cellular phone bill?
那个手机帐单记录怎么样？
We're pulling Loomis's account. We won't know anything until the morning.
正在检查卢米斯的帐号， 明早才有结果
Oh, come on!
噢，快点！
You think he did it?
你认为是他干的？
Twenty years ago, I would've said, "Not a chance."
二十年前，我会说“绝对不会”
But these kids today... damned if I know.
但是现在的孩子... 谁知道呢？
- Hey, Dewey, can we go now? - Hold on a second.
- 嘿，杜威，我们可以走了吗？ - 等一下
- Goddamn it, Dewey! - What did Mama tell you?
- 讨厌，杜威！ - 妈妈是怎么跟你说的？
When I wear this badge, you treat me like a man of the law!
当我戴上这警徽时， 你应该把我当成执法人员！
I'm sorry, Deputy Dewey-boy, but we're ready to go.
对不起，副治安官杜威朋友， 我们准备走了
- Now, okay? -  Whoa.
- 现在，好不好？ -  哈哈
Take 'em out the back way. Avoid that circus out there.
带他们从后面走 避开前门那些耍杂的
- Come on. - Don't touch me!
- 来吧 - 别碰我！
- He's my superior. - Janitors are your superior.
- 他是我的上级 - 看门的才是你的上级呢
Let's get back to work!
来，大家开始工作！
- Isn't there a back way out of this building? - Yeah.
- 这栋楼有没有后门？ - 有
Down that alley, I think.
应该是顺着这条小路
You guys just stay here. I'm gonna get the car.
你们呆在这儿， 我去取车
Don't move. Don't make a sound.
别走开，别出声
There she is. Sidney!
她在那儿希德内！
Hi, that's some night. What happened? Are you all right?
嗨，真是 发生什么了？你没事吧？
She's not answering any questions. Just leave us alone.
她不会回答你的问题的 别烦我们
No, Tatum, it's okay. She's just doin' her job, right, Gale?
不，塔特姆，没事 人家只是在工作而已是吧，基尔？
- Yes, that's right. - So, how's the book?
- 是呀，没错 - 那本书怎样了？
Well, it'll be out later this year.
艾今年迟些时候才能出来
Oh, I'll look for it.
哦，我一定会看的
I'll send you a copy.
我会送你一本的
Jeez.
哎呀！
-  Nice shot. -  Bitch.
-  干得好！ -  婊子
No, I mean, camera shot.
不，我是说摄像干得不错
Where'd you learn to punch like that?
你从哪儿学会这样打人的？
God, I loved it. "I'll send you a copy."
老天，我真喜欢这个 “我会送你一本的”
Bam! Bitch went down.
梆！婊子倒下了
"I'll send you a copy." Bam! Sid... Superbitch!
“我会送你一本的” 梆！希德... 超级婊子！
You are so cool.
你真是太酷了
Thought you might want some ice for that right hook.
打出那记右勾拳后， 你的手可能需要些冰块
Thanks.
谢谢
I'll be right next door. Try to get some sleep.
我就在隔壁，想睡一会
Yeah, yeah.
好吧，好吧
Do you really think Billy did it?
你真认为是比利干的吗？
He was there, Tatum.
他当时在那儿，塔特姆
He was destined to have a flaw. I knew he was too perfect.
人注定会有缺陷的， 他以前在我眼里太完美了
Telephone, honey.
电话，亲爱的
- Who is it? - It's for Sid.
- 是谁？ - 找希德的
My dad?
我爸爸？
- I don't think so. -  Take a message.
- 恐怕不是 -  叫他留言
No, um, I'll get it.
不，嗯，我来接
How's she doin'?
她怎么样？
Hello.
喂
Hello, Sidney.
你好，希德内
No!
不！
Poor Billy-boyfriend.
你男朋友比利真可怜
An innocent guy doesn't stand a chance with you.
那个无辜的家伙，再也 没有机会和你在一起了
- Leave me alone! - Looks like you fingered the wrong guy... again.
- 放过我！ - 看起来你又一次指控错人了
- Who are you? - Dewey! - Hang up, Sid.
- 你是谁？ - 杜威！ - 挂电话，希德
Don't worry. You'll find out soon enough.
别担心你很快就会知道的
I promise.
我发誓
What?
怎么了？
- What? - What?
- 怎么了？ - 怎么了？
Hello?
喂？
Sidney Prescott, who escaped a vicious attack last night
昨晚逃过了那场恶性袭击事件的希德内·普里斯科特
is the daughter of Maureen Prescott...
是毛里恩·普里斯科特的女儿...
who was brutally killed last year...
毛里恩去年被残忍地谋杀...
when convicted murderer Cotton Weary broke into their home
已被裁定有罪的凶手科顿·威而瑞，当时闯入他们家里
and savagely raped and tortured the deceased.
野蛮地强奸并折磨了死者
Cotton Weary is currently awaiting appeal for the death sentence...
科顿·威而瑞目前正在 为其死刑判决上诉...
handed down after the young Sidney testified against him.
在年轻的希德内指证他后， 他被判处死罪
She was the key witness in the state's case against the...
她是那个案件中的关键证人...
It's never gonna stop, is it?
他们真是没完没了，是吧？
Billy was released.
比利被释放了
His cellular bill was clean. He didn't make those calls.
他的手机记录没有问题， 不是他打的那些电话
We're checkin' every cellular account in the county.
我们正在检查本县内 所有手机的通话记录
Any calls made to you or Casey Becker are being cross-referenced.
所有打给你或凯西·贝克尔 的电话都会被对照参考
It's gonna take some time, but we'll find him.
需要些时间，但我们一定会找到他的
Okay?
好了
Don't worry, Sid, it's school. You'll be safe here.
别担心，希德，这儿是学校 你会很安全的
So how does it feel to be almost brutally butchered?
差一点儿就被残忍地宰割， 你有什么感想？
- Hey, leave her alone! - People wanna know. They have a right to know.
- 嘿，别烦她！ - 人们想知道他们有权知道
-  Leave her alone. - How does it feel?
-  别烦她 - 感觉如何？
She just wants to get an education. Turn that thing off.
她只是来上学的把那些东西关掉
What?
什么？
Just a sec.
等一会儿
Stop right there.
停那儿别动
I'm not here to fight. I just need to talk.
我不是来打架的 我需要和你谈谈
Kenny, camera, now!
肯尼，马上准备摄象机！
Off the record. No camera.
不用记录，不要摄像
- Forget it. - Please? You owe me.
- 忘了吧 - 什么？你欠我的
- I owe you shit! - You owe my mother!
- 我欠你狗屎啊 - 你欠我母亲的！
Your mother's murder was last year's hottest court case.
你母亲的谋杀案是去年最轰动的庭案
Somebody was gonna write about it.
总会有个人为此写书的
And it had to be you with all your lies and bullshit theories.
并且这个人还就得像你一样，充满了谎言和狗屎理论
What is your problem? You got what you wanted.
你有什么毛部 你还想要什么？
Cotton Weary's in jail.
科顿·威而瑞被关进监狱了
They're gonna gas him. A book is not gonna change that.
并将被执行毒刑 一本书根本改变不了这个
Do you still think he's innocent?
你还认为他是无辜的？
Your testimony put him away. It doesn't really matter what I think.
你的证词使他定罪 我怎么想根本无关紧要
During the trial, you did all those stories about me. You called me a liar.
当时审讯时，你就编造了那些故事， 还说我在撒谎
I think you falsely identified him, yes.
是的，我认为你认错人了
- Have you talked to Cotton? - Many times.
- 你跟科顿谈过吗？ - 很多次
And has his story changed?
那你对他所说的那些故事改变过吗？
Not one word.
一点儿也没有
He admits to having sex with your mother, but that's all.
他只承认和你母亲有过性关系
He's lying. She never would've touched him.
他在撒谎， 我母亲根本碰都不会碰他
He raped her, and then he...
他强奸了她，并且...
He butchered her. Her blood was all over his coat.
肢解了她 他的外套上占满了我妈的血
He was drunk that night.
他那天晚上喝多了
He left his coat at your house after your mother seduced him.
你妈引诱他后，他把外套落在你家了
I saw him leave wearing it.
我看见他离开时穿着
No, you saw someone leave wearing that coat.
不，你看见的是另 一个人穿的那件外套
The same someone who planted it in Cotton's car, framing him.
那个人又把外套放进科顿的车里， 陷害他
No. Cotton murdered my mother.
不，科顿杀了我妈
You're not so sure anymore, are you?
你不像以前那样确信了，是吗？
Nice welt, sweetie. Let's go, Sid.
脸肿得好漂亮艾亲爱的 我们走，希德
The killer's still on the loose, isn't he?
杀手还在逍遥法外，对不？
- Come on, Sid. - Those murders are related.
- 走吧，希德 - 这些谋杀是有联系的
I'm sorry I mangled your face.
对不起，我把你的脸打肿了
- Sidney, don't go! - Just stop, all right?
- 希德内，别走！ - 别跟来，知道不？
Jesus Christ!
老天！
An innocent man on death row. A killer still on the loose.
无辜的人等着被执行死刑， 而真正的凶手却逍遥法外
Kenny, tell me I'm dreaming.
肯尼，告诉我我是在做梦
You wanna go live?
你想现场直播这些？
Not so fast. We don't have anything concrete.
别着急，我们还没有确切的线索
You can't just sit on it.
你不能一直拖延下去
I know! That's why we need proof.
我知道！ 这就是为什么我们迫切需要证据
If I'm right about this, I could save a man's life.
如果我这次对了， 我就挽救了一个人的生命
Do you know what that could do for my book sales?
你知道那会对我写的书 的销量有什么样的影响吗？
This is a mistake. I shouldn't be here.
这真是个错误，我不该在这儿的
I want you to meet me right here after class, okay, Sid?
我希望你下课后来这儿 见我好吗，希德内？
All right.
好的
Hey, I haven't seen Billy around. Is he really pissed?
嘿，怎么没见到比利 难道他真的很恼火？
Oh, you mean after you branded him the Candyman?
哦，你以为你只是 把糖纸贴在他身上？
- No, his heart's broken. Ow! - Stu!
- 不，他是伤心透了哎哟！ - 斯图！
Why are they doing this?
他们为什么要这样？
Are you kidding me? Look at this place. It's like Christmas.
你开玩笑吗？ 看看这周围，像是过圣诞
- Stupidity leak. - Ow. Easy.
- 别犯傻了 - 哎哟，轻点
Sidney!
希德内！
- Ow! - Jesus, shit!
- 哎哟！ - 老天，真是！
It's just me.
是我
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. You still think it's me.
哇，哇，哇，哇 你还认为是我干的？
No. No, I-I don't.
不，不，我不是
It's just... somebody was there.
只是... 确实有人在那儿
Billy, someone tried to kill me.
比利，有人想杀我
I know, I know. The cops said I scared him away.
我知道，我知道警察说我把他吓走了
It wasn't me, Sid.
那人不是我，希德内
I know. He called me again last night at Tatum's house.
我知道昨晚在塔特姆家里，他又打电话给我了
You see? It couldn't have been me. I was in jail.
你看，那不可能是我我在监狱
Remember?
记得吗？
I'm so... sorry. Please understand.
非常对...对不起 请理解我
Understand what?
理解什么？
That I have a girlfriend who would rather accuse me...
难道是我有一个宁愿指控我为...
of being a psychopathic killer than touch me?
变态杀手，而不愿摸摸我的女友？
You know that's not true.
你知道你说的不是真的
- Then what is it? - What... is it?
- 那是什么？ - 什么...是吗？
Billy, I was attacked and nearly filleted last night!
比利，我昨晚被袭击， 差点儿被大卸八块！
I mean between us.
我是说我们之间的关系
You haven't been the same since...
你变了，自从...
- Since your mother died. - Is your brain leaking?
- 你妈妈死后 - 你脑子又问题呀？
My mom was killed. I can't believe you're bringing this up!
我妈被谋杀了 真不能相信你又提起这档子事
- It's been a year. - Tomorrow! One year tomorrow.
- 已经一年了 - 明天！到明天一年
I think it's time you got over that.
我觉得现在是该你从 中恢复过来的时侯了
When my mom left my dad, I accepted it.
当我妈离开我爸的时侯， 我接受了
That's the way it is.
事情就是这个样子的
She's not coming back.
她不会再回来了
Your parents split up. This is not the same thing.
你父母离婚了 这不是一码事
Your mom left town.
你妈只是离开了我们镇
She's not lying in a coffin somewhere.
并没有呆在某处的一个棺材里
Okay, okay, I'm sorry. It's a bad analogy.
好吧，好吧，对不起 这真是一个糟糕的比较
It's just that...
我只是想...
I want my girlfriend back.
让我以前样子的女友恢复回来
Sid!
希德！
Billy, I am sorry if my traumatized life...
比利，对不起， 如果我受到创伤的生活...
is an inconvenience to you and your perfect existence.
给你和你完美的存在 造成了不便的话
What? Wh... Nobody said that. Sid!
什么？什... 没人那样说，希德！
Stupid.
真蠢
You make me so sick!
你们使我恶心！
Your entire havoc-inducing, thieving, whoring generation disgusts me!
你们这些破坏狂、小偷 及娼妓的一代真令我恶心！
So, two of your fellow students...
你们中的两个学生...
just savagely murdered...
刚被残忍地谋杀了...
and this is the way you show your compassion and sensitivity, huh?
难道这就是你们表现出 的同情心和伤感吗，嗯？
Let me tell you something. You're both expelled! Get out!
我告诉你们， 你们俩都被开除了！滚！
Come on, Mr. Himbry! It was just a joke.
得了，希伯瑞先生！ 这只是个玩笑
That's not fair!
这太不公平了
You're absolutely right. It is not fair.
你说得对极了， 这就是不公平
Fairness would be to rip your insides out...
如果公平的话，我就该 把你们的肠子都挖出来...
hang you from a tree so we can expose you...
再把你们吊在树上，让那些...
for the heartless, desensitized little shits that you are.
像你们一样无情无义，没有丝毫感觉的小杂种们都来看
She was never attacked. I think she made it all up.
她没有被袭击过 我觉得一切都是她编的
-  Why would she lie about it? - For attention!
-  那她为什么要撒谎 - 为了吸引注意力呗
The girl has some serious issues.
那个女孩有严重的问题
What if she did it?
如果是她干的呢？
What if Sidney killed Casey and Steve?
如果是希德内杀了凯西和史迪夫呢？
Why would she do that?
她为什么要那样干？
Maybe she had the hots for Steve and killed them both in a jealous rage.
可能是她特别想上史迪夫， 因为嫉妒而杀了他们俩
What would Sidney want with Steve?
为什么希德内想上史迪夫？
She has her own bubble-butt boyfriend.
她自己有个翘屁股的性感男友比利呀？
Maybe she's a slut just like her mother.
有可能她也是个荡妇， 就象她妈一样
- You're evil. - Please, it's a common fact.
- 你真恶毒 - 得了，这是常识
Her mother was a tramp.
她妈是个妓女
Cut some slack. She watched her mom get butchered.
如果有机会，她会看着她妈被杀的
And it fucked her up royally. Think about it.
想想看，那会使她多么兴奋呀
Her mother's death leaves her disturbed and hostile.
她妈的死使她心理变得不正常， 还充满敌意
In a cruel and inhumane world, she's delusional.
在这个残酷而不公平的世界， 她太天真妄想了
Where is God? Etcetera. Completely suicidal.
如“上帝在哪儿呀？”，等等等等， 完全是自取灭亡
One day she snaps. She wants to kill herself...
有一天她突然受不了， 她想自杀...
but she realizes that teen suicide is out this year...
但是她认识到今年少女 自杀已经过时了...
and homicide is a much healthier, therapeutic expression.
谋杀会更有利于健康， 如果从治疗学上来表述的话
Where do you get this shit?
你从哪儿学到的这些狗屁？
Ricki Lake.
Ricki Lake说的
You are pathetic.
你真是可悲呀
Pathetic.
可悲的
Sidney.
希德内
Is someone there?
有人吗？
In what appears to be a prank...
在看起来是恶作剧的事件中...
several students were seen wearing scary masks.
有人看见几个学生戴着恐怖面具
School officials have yet to comment...
学校当局还没有对此发表评论...
but this is known to be the same costume worn by the killer.
现在知道这些面具和 凶手戴的是一样的
Seventeen-year-old Casey Becker and her boyfriend
17岁的凯西·贝克尔和她的男友
Steven Orth have already lost their lives.
史迪夫·厄斯已经被杀了
Who's next?
谁是下一个呢？
You can literally feel the fear on this campus.
你可以确切地感觉到 恐惧弥漫在这校园中
Hi! Gale Weathers, field correspondent, "Top Story."
嗨！我是基尔·唯茨，《头条消息》的现场记者
I know who you are, Miss Weathers.
我知道你是谁， 唯茨小姐
- How's the eye? - It's productive. Is there a problem on campus?
- 眼睛怎么样？ - 快好了校园里有什么问题吗？
No, everything's under control.
没有，一切都在控制中
- Of course. You're here. - You're not supposed to be here.
- 当然，你在这儿嘛 - 可是你不该在这儿
I know. I should be in New York covering the Sharon Stone stalker...
我知道我应该在纽约报道 骚扰莎朗·斯通的人...
but who knew?
但是谁知道呢？
You look awfully young to be a police officer.
你看起来这么年轻， 不像一个警官呀
I'm 25 years old.
我已经25了
You know, in a demographic study...
知道吗，在一项统计调查中...
I proved to be most popular amongst males 11 to 24.
我最受11到24岁的男性观众欢迎
Guess I just missed you.
看来我正好错过了你这个年纪
Of course, you don't look a day over 12.
不过，你看起来还不到12岁
Except in that upper torso area.
要是不看你强壮的躯干的话
- Does the force require you to work out? - No, ma'am.
- 是警察都要求锻炼吗？ - 不，女士
'Cause of my boyish good looks...
那是为了弥补我这张孩子 气的漂亮脸蛋儿...
muscle mass has increased my acceptance as a serious police officer.
如果有一身肌肉的话， 可以增加我当高级警官的机会
I need your attention now, kids.
同学们，请注意
Due to the recent events that have occurred...
由于最近发生的事件...
effective immediately, all classes are suspended until further notice.
学校决定停课，何时开课另行通知 此项宣布立即生效
The Woodsboro police department has issued a citywide curfew...
伍兹士堡警察局发布 了全城范围的宵禁令...
beginning at 9:00 tonight.
从今天晚上9点开始
Looks like we've got a serial killer on our hands.
看样子我们遇到了一个连环杀手
Serial killer's not really accurate.
“连环杀手”这词并不准确
Gotta knock off a couple more to get that title.
凶手只有再杀几个 才能得到这个头衔
Well, we can hope, can't we?
艾我们有这个希望，不是吗？
I mean, we certainly don't have any leads.
我的意思是，我们确实没有任何线索
- Have you located Sidney's father yet? - No, not yet.
- 你找到了希德内的父亲了吗？ - 还没有
He's not a suspect, is he?
他不是嫌疑人，对不？
We haven't ruled him out as a... possibility.
我们还没有排除他的...可能性
- If you'll excuse me. - I'm sorry. Am I keeping you?
- 失陪了 - 对不起，我妨碍了你吗？
If I may say so, Miss Weathers...
可以这样说，唯茨小姐...
you are much prettier in person.
你真人看起来漂亮多了
So you do watch the show.
那你真的看我的节目了
I'm 25. I was 24 for a whole year.
我今年25 我去年一年都是24
Please, call me Gale!
请叫我基尔吧！
It was just some sick fuck having a laugh, Sidney.
那只是某些病态的杂种 假扮了逗你的，希德内
No, it was him, Tatum. I know it.
不，是他，塔特姆 我知道
You're not to pee alone anymore.
你不要再一个人去卫生间了
If you pee, I pee. Is that clear?
如果你去，我也去明白吗？
I don't know what you did, Sidney.
我不管你做了什么，希德内
But on behalf of the entire student body, we all say, "Thank you!"
但是代表全体学生， 我们要说：“谢谢你”
- Drop it, Stu. - I say...
- 别说了，斯图 - 我宣布...
an impromptu party tonight, my house.
今晚在我家举办一个即兴聚会，
Celebrate this little siesta. What do you say?
来庆祝学校的停课 你说如何？
Are you serious?
你是认真的？
This little vixen...
差不多吧，你这个小泼妇...
doesn't invite the entire world, we'll be fine.
放心吧，不会邀请所有人的
Intimate gathering, intimate friends.
只是几个老朋友亲密的聚会
What do you say, Sid?
你说怎么样，希德？
I mean, pathos could have its perks.
我的意思是，老这样痛苦也不是办法， 来轻松一下吧
Totally protected. Yo, I am so buff.
安全方面绝对没有问题 喱你看我是多么强壮
I got you covered, girl.
姑娘们，我会保护你们的
Come on, Sid. For me? It could be fun.
来吧，希德 给我个面子，很好玩的
Okay. Whatever.
既然这样，好吧
Yeah? Nice.
是吗？太好了！
Cool. You guys bring food, all right?
棒极了你们带食品，好不好？
Yes?
谁？
Hello?
谁呀？
- Damn little shits. - What'd you call me? Huh?
- 他妈的小混蛋 - 你叫我什么？嗯？
- Not you, Fred. -  You prick.
- 不是说你，弗雷德 -  你个笨蛋
Aaaah! Aaah!
啊啊
Ohhhhh!
哦！
School's out for summer
学校放暑假了
School's out
学校放假了
What if Cotton Weary is telling the truth?
如果科顿·威而瑞说的是真的， 怎么办？
Maybe he was having an affair with your mom.
他也许的确和你妈妈有一腿
I mean, your dad was always out of town on business. Maybe...
我的意思是， 你爸爸常常出差不在家也许...
Maybe your mom was just a very unhappy woman.
也许你妈妈只是一个 非常不快乐的女人
If they were having an affair,
如果他们真的有一腿
how come Cotton couldn't prove it in court?
那科顿为什么不能在法庭上证明？
Well, you can't prove a rumor.
嗯，谣言是没法被证明的
That's why it's a rumor.
这就是为什么叫谣言的缘故
Right. Created by that little tabloid twit Gale Weathers.
对，是那个白痴小报记者 基尔·唯茨造的谣
It goes further back, Sid.
背后还有更多的，希德
There's been talk about other men.
还有有关和其他男人的传闻
And you believe it.
那你相信了？
Well, you can only hear that Richard Gere gerbil story so many times...
唉，谣言听得太多了
before you have to start believing it.
你就不得不开始相信
Oh, I'm sorry.
哎，对不起
Y-You know, if I was wrong about Cotton Weary
你-你知道，如果我对科顿·威而瑞 的指控错了的话
then... the killer's still out there.
那么...凶手还在那儿
Don't go there, Sid.
不要去那儿，希德
You're starting to sound like some Wes Carpenter flick or something.
你说的听起来像韦斯和卡彭特，拍的电影之类的东东了
Don't freak yourself, okay? We've got a long night ahead of us. Okay?
别想得太多，好不？我们还要度过 一个很长的夜晚呢
Let's boogie.
让我们跳起来
It's alive!
还是活的！
- Henry   - Oh, in the name of God, now I know
- 亨利   - 噢，以上帝的名义，现在我知道
Excuse me, dude.
对不起，伙计
- Watch it, jerk. - I'm sorry.
- 注意点，呆子 - 对不起
Ohhhh!
哎呀！
Dork.
混蛋！
Jesus, this place is packed tonight, man.
老天，今儿晚上这里可真挤呀，老兄
We had a run in the mass murder section.
来租多重谋杀案之类的片子的人可真多
Comin' to my fiesta?
参加我家的聚会吗？
Yeah, I'm off early. Curfew, you know.
当然，今天我放工早 你知道，有宵禁
What's that werewolf movie with E.T.'s mom in it?
那个狼人的电影叫什么？ 里面还有E.T.的妈妈
"The Howling." Horror. Straight ahead.
是《狼嗥》，恐怖片区一直往前就是
Okay, thanks.
好的，谢谢
Oh, now that's in poor taste.
噢，现在那种片子根本不对人的胃口了
What?
什么？
If you were the only suspect in a senseless bloodbath
如果在一场毫无意义的大屠杀中，只有一个人是嫌疑犯
would you be standing in the horror section?
你还会看吗？
What? It was just a misunderstanding. He didn't do anything.
什么？那只是一个误会 不是他干的
You're such a little lapdog.
你真是个小哈巴狗
He's got "killer" printed all over his forehead.
你看，他的整个额头上都写着“杀手”两个字
Ohhh-kay!
是吗？
Really? Well, why'd the cops let him go, smart guy?
真的吗？ 那警察为什么把他放了，大葱头？
Obviously they don't watch enough movies. This is standard horror movie stuff.
显然他们看的电影还不够多，这是标准的恐怖电影情节
"Prom Night" revisited, man.
简直是《毕业舞会之夜》再现，老兄
Yeah? Why would he wanna kill his own girlfriend?
是吗？那他为什么想杀自己的女朋友？
There's always some stupid, bullshit reason to kill your girlfriend.
总会有那么些愚蠢而没道理的，原因去杀自己的女朋友
- Oh? - That's the beauty of it all: simplicity.
- 哦？ - 这就是整个事情的可取之处：简单
Besides, if it gets too complicated, you lose your target audience.
再说了，如果搞得太复杂， 你把观众都吓跑了
Well, what's his reason?
那好，可是他的动机是什么？
Maybe Sidney wouldn't have sex with him.
也许希德内不愿和他上床
What, is she savin' herself for you?
什么？难道她 准备把第一次留给你？
Maybe.
有可能
Now that Billy tried to mutilate her, do you think Sid would go out with me?
既然现在比利要害她，你说希德会不会跟我出去约会？
No, I don't at all. No.
不，打死我也不会这样认为 不可能的
You know who I think it is?
你知道我觉得是谁干的吗？
You know, I think it's her father.
知道吗？我觉得是她老爹干的
Why can't they find her pops, man?
老兄，知道他们为什么找不到她老爹？
Because he's probably dead.
因为他有可能已经死了
His body will come poppin' up in the last reel somewhere!
他的尸体最后肯定会在某处出现！
Eyes gouged out, fingers cut off, teeth knocked out!
眼珠被挖了出来，手指被割了下来，牙齿也被敲掉了！
- The police are always off track with this shit. - Man!
- 警察在这些案件中总是找错了方向 - 哇！
If they'd watch "Prom Night,"
如果他们看了《毕业舞会之夜》
they'd save time.
他们就不会费那么多时间了
There's a formula to it. A very simple formula!
有一个规则，很简单的一个规则
Everybody's a suspect!
那就是：每个人都是嫌疑犯！
I'm telling you, the dad's a red herring. It's Billy.
我告诉你，她父亲只是一个烟幕弹 真凶是比利
How do we know you're not the killer? Huh?
我们怎么知道你不是凶手呢？嗯？
- Huh? - Hi, Billy.
- 嗯？ - 嗨，比利
Maybe your movie-freaked mind lost its reality button.
你想没有，你是不是看电影看糊涂了
You ever think of that?
已经分不清什么是现实， 什么是电影里的了？
You're absolutely right. I'm the first to admit it.
你说的很对我现在第一个承认这点
If this were a scary movie, l'd be the prime suspect.
如果这是一场恐怖电影，那我就是 头号嫌疑犯
That's right.
这就对了
And what would be your motive?
那你的动机是什么？
It's the millennium.
都快到新世纪了，
Motives are incidental.
动机根本不重要
"Millennium". Hmm.
“新世纪”，嗯
"Millennium". I like that. That's good. It's the millennium.
“新世纪”，我喜欢这个 很好，现在是新世纪
Good kid.
好孩子
"Millennium". Good word, my man.
“新世纪”，好词，老兄
Are you telling me that's not a killer?
你是说他不是杀手吗？
Sure is quiet.
多么安静呀
God, look at this place.
天哪，看看这个地方
It's "The Town That Dreaded Sundown."
太像《杀出魔鬼镇》里的镜头了
Yeah, I saw that movie.
是艾我也看过那个电影
It's about a killer in Texas, huh?
讲的是德州一个杀手的故事，对吧？
- Mmm. - Hey, Sid, just think.
- 嗯 - 嗨，希德，你想一想，
If they make a movie about you, who's gonna play you?
如果有人要拍一个有关你的电影， 你说谁会来演你？
I shudder to think.
我有点害怕去想这个
I see you as a young Meg Ryan myself.
我看你就像年轻时的梅格·瑞恩
Thanks, Dewey. With my luck,
谢谢，杜威如果我猜得准的话
they'd cast Tori Spelling.
他们会让托瑞·斯培林去演的
I'm just gonna be a few minutes.
我只需要几分钟时间
You girls don't go too far.
你们不要走得太远了
Is Billy gonna be there tonight?
比利今晚会来吗？
He'd better not be. I told Stu to keep his mouth shut.
他最好别来 我已经叫斯图别告诉他了
I think we can live without the endorphin rush for one night.
我想我们可以忘掉痛苦， 快乐地过一个晚上
Billy's right, you know. Whenever he touches me, I just can't relax.
比利说得对，你知道 他一摸我，我就感到不自在
So you have a few intimacy issues as a result of your mother's untimely death.
可能是你妈妈死得太早，影响了你这方面的正常发展
That's no big deal. You'll thaw out.
没什么大不了的， 你心头的冰块会融化的
Yeah, but he has been so patient with me with all the sex stuff.
是艾可是他在性这 方面已经够有耐心了
How many guys would put up with a girlfriend who's sexually anorexic?
你说有几个男孩子能 忍受性冷淡的女友呢？
Billy and his penis don't deserve you, all right?
比利和他的阳具配不上你，好不好？
Dewey, where the hell you been?
杜威，你他妈跑哪儿去了？
I was keepin' an eye on Sidney, uh...
我一直在看着希德内，嗯...
- Thought you quit. - I did. But damn it...
- 你不是戒了吗？ - 是戒了，但是他妈的...
Dewey, Vital Phone just faxed us.
杜威，威特尔电话公司刚刚 给我们发来了传真
Those calls are listed to Neil Prescott,
那些电话是属于尼尔·普里斯科特
Sidney's father.
也就是希德内老爹的帐户上的
He made the calls with a cellular phone. It's been confirmed.
现在已经证实是他用手机打的
There's no way a cellular coulda been cloned?
难道不可能复制一个同样的手机吗？
There's more. Guess what tomorrow is.
还有，猜猜看明天是什么
The anniversary of his wife's death.
是他老婆死去的周年纪念日
We'll keep the roadblocks and the curfew in effect through the night.
今天整个晚上，我们都要设置路障， 并执行宵禁令
If he's not picked up by morning, then we'll do a house-to-house.
如果到早上还没有抓到他， 我们就要挨家挨户去搜查
- Where's Sidney? - She's with my sister.
- 希德内在哪儿？ - 她和我妹妹在一起
- You want me to bring her in? - Naw.
- 你想让我把她带到这儿吗？ - 不用了
Not just yet.
还不到时侯
Let's find Neil first, make sure he's our man.
让我们先找到尼尔， 确认他是我们想要的真凶
You stay close to Sidney.
你要好好看着希德内
Don't let her out of your sight.
别让她离开你的视线
Yes, sir.
是，长官
All right, you girls have fun.
好了，姑娘们，你们去玩吧
Not too much fun, or I'll bust ya.
别太过火了，否则把你们都捉起来
- Bye. - Bye, Sid.
- 拜 - 拜，希德
Here, kids!
我们来了，孩子们！
Oh! That's absurd.
噢！真可笑
You guys were tardy for the party, so we started without you.
你们办事太拖拉了， 晚会已经开始了
My man!
不错，哥儿们！
Shh.
嘘
Were we spotted?
我们被发现了吗？
I don't think so. Go get the camera.
不会的去拿摄像机
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare ya.
对不起，我不是故意吓你的
- Deputy, that's okay. - What brings you to these parts?
- 副警长，没事儿 - 你怎么也来这个聚会了？
Well, you just never know when or where a story will break.
是艾 你根本不知道何时何地出现新闻
Not much of a story here. Just a bunch of kids cuttin' it loose.
这儿没什么新闻， 只是一帮孩子在闹哄
Then what are you doing here?
那你在这儿干什么？
Just keepin' an eye on things.
只是在这里看着他们
I'm gonna check the party out.
我要去看看聚会怎么样了
- Do you mind if I join you? - Not at all.
- 介意我跟你一块去吗？ - 一点儿也不
Let me just get my coat. Thanks.
等我先拿一下外套，谢谢
- All right. - Yeah, I'm fine.
- 好了 - 没关系的
Oh! Yeah.
哦！对了
- How many "Evil Deads"? - One! Two!
- 谁看《尸变》？ - 一个！两个！
- How many "Hellraisers"? - Hellraiser right here.
- 谁看《猛鬼追魂》？ - 我看
"The Fog," "Terror Train," "Prom Night."
像《冤魂不息》，《死亡列车》，《毕业舞会之夜》
How come Jamie Lee Curtis is in all of these movies?
怎么每个片子里都有 杰米·李·柯蒂斯呀？
She's the... scream queen.
她是...尖叫之皇后
- With a set of lungs like that, she should be. - Yeah.
- 看看她那样的肺，不是才怪呢 - 是啊
Tits. See?
是胸部，明白吗？
Oh, I'll get it.
哦，我去开
Hey, Tate, grab another beer, would ya?
嗨，塔特，再拿一瓶啤酒来，好吗？
There's more beer in the garage.
车库里有更多的啤酒
What am l, the beer wench?
把我当什么了？啤酒侍应？
- She was nominated for "Terror Train." - Oh, yeah?
- 她因为《死亡列车》而被提名 - 哦，是吗？
You are not gonna believe who's here! It's that chick from "Top Story"!
你们不会相信谁来了 是那个《头条消息》的女的
- Gale Weathers? - Here. Yeah.
- 基尔·唯茨？ - 是她，没错
You're under age, son.
小子，你还不到年纪
I'm kiddin'. Have a good time.
开个玩笑好好玩
-  Dewey. - Hi.
-  杜威 - 嗨
Dewey.
杜威
- What is she doing here? - She's with me!
- 她来这儿干什么？ - 她跟我一起来的
- I'm just checkin' things out. - So you did.
- 我只是来查看查看 - 既然已经看过了，
Now leave, and take your media mouth with you.
你快点离开这儿吧， 把你的小道消息跟班也带走
- I just think you're awesome. - Oh, thank you very much.
- 我觉得你真是了不起 - 哦，非常感谢
- I watch your show religiously. - That's great.
- 我一直忠实地看你的节目 - 太好了
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嗨 - 嗨
I need a camera
我需要一个相机
- Have you found my father? - I'm afraid not.
- 找到我爸爸了吗？ - 恐怕还没有
-  Should I be worried? -  Not yet.
-  我该担心吗？ -  现在还不必
That's the one I want... "Halloween."
那是我想看的《鬼节》
Mmm.
唔
Jesus!
天哪！
Tatum, it's okay.
塔特姆，没事儿的
Shit.
怎么回事！
Hey, shitheads!
嗨，讨厌鬼！
Hello!
喂！
Shit. Piss.
混蛋，真讨厌
Is that you, Randy?
是你吗，兰迪？
Cute. What movie is this from?
好了，这又是从哪出电影学来的？
"I Spit On Your Garage"?
是《我唾弃你的坟墓》？
Lose the outfit. If Sidney sees it, she'll flip.
把面具脱了吧 要是希德内看到了，她会发疯的
Oh, you wanna play psycho killer?
哦，你想扮变态杀手？
Can I be the helpless victim?
我可以扮无助的受害者吗？
Okay, let's see... No, please don't kill me, Mr. Ghost Face.
好吧，我们来...  不，请别杀我，鬼脸先生
I wanna be in the sequel!
我还想演续集呢
Cut, Casper. That's a wrap.
停，小鬼头 电影结束了
Randy, what the hell are you doing? Aaah!
兰迪，你究竟想干什么？啊
Aaaah!
啊...！
Fucker!
混蛋！
Aaah!
啊
Aaah! Aaaah!
啊啊
- Happy curfew. - Nice party, Stu.
- 宵禁快乐 - 晚会不错，斯图
Tatum, come on!
塔特姆，快来！
There's nobody here but us chickens!
这儿除了我们几个女的， 没有别人了
Do you know where she is?
你知道她在哪儿吗？
No, I haven't seen her.
不知道， 我一直没有见到她
Aaah!
啊
Oh. Billy. Hey.
噢，比利，嗨
Billy. Hmm. What are you doin' here?
比利，嗯 你来这儿干什么？
I was hoping I could talk to Sid alone.
我希望和希德单独谈谈
You know, if Tatum sees you here, she'll draw blood.
你知道，要是塔特姆看见你在这儿， 她会不高兴的
Why don't you go up to my parents' room?
你们为什么不去我父母房里呢？
You know, you guys can talk, whatever.
在那儿，你们可以谈话， 或干其它别的
Subtlety, Stu. You should look it up.
斯图，注意点你的语气
No, i-it's okay. We do need to talk.
不，没-没关系 我们是需要谈谈
Oooh! Oww.
唔！哈
What's Leatherface doin' here?
这个杀人狂来干吗？
Cute. He came to make up.
别装了他是来弥补关系的
There goes my chance with Sid. Damn it.
那不没我的什么机会了，真倒霉
As if. That's all I'm sayin'.
好像是我能说的就是这些喽
As if.
好像是
Oh, really, Alicia?
哦，真的吗？
"As if." I'm gonna go check on them.
“好像是” 我要去看看他们
- Come on! -  It was nice to meet all of you.
- 快点出来！ -  见到你们真是很高兴
You're a genius.
你真是个天才
- Oh, shit. - What?
- 哦，真倒霉 - 什么？
- I got a delay. -  How long is it?
- 信号有延时 -  多长延迟？
I don't know. What'd it take you to walk from the house, 30 seconds?
不知道你从那房子走到这儿 要花多长时间？30秒？
It'll be fine. Just record it. Oh, the placement is perfect.
没关系，尽管录下来就是了 哇！放的位置真好
- Tell me, Kenneth... - Hmm?
- 告诉我， 肯尼思... - 嗯？
Has a cheesy tabloid journalist ever won the Pulitzer?
有没有一个下流小报记者 曾经赢得过普利策奖？
Well, first time for everything.
唔，每件事情都有第一次的
You're damn right.
你简直太对了！
S-So, um...
那...，嗯...
So...
那...
I'm sorry.
对不起
I've been selfish, and I want to apologize.
我太自私了，我应该道歉
No, Billy, I-I'm...
不，比利，我-我是...
the one who's been selfish and self-absorbed...
那个自私而又太专注于 自己的想法的人...
with all this post-traumatic stress.
都是由于这些受到创伤后的压力所致
- You lost your mom. - Yeah, I know, but you're right.
- 你失去了母亲 - 是的，我知道你说得对...
Enough is enough.
什么事都有一个限度
I can't wallow in the grief process forever...
我不能一直沉浸在悲伤中...
and...
而且...
and I can't...
而且，我不能...
keep lying to myself about who my mom was.
一直对自己撒谎， 认为我妈不是那样的人
Yeah, I think I'm really...
是的，我觉得我真是被我的想法...
scared...
吓坏了
that I'm gonna turn out just like her, you know?
你知道吗？ 我害怕有一天变成和我妈妈一样的人
Like "The Bad Seed" or somethin'.
类似《坏种》中的情节那样
And I know it doesn't make sense.
虽然我知道这些想法太荒唐
Yeah, it does.
不，不荒唐
Hmm.
嗯
It's like Jodie Foster in "The Silence of the Lambs"...
就像朱迪·福斯特在 《沉默的羔羊》中...
when she keeps having flashbacks of her dead father.
不断地回忆自己死去的父亲那样
But this is life.
但是，这是现实生活
This isn't a movie.
这不是电影
Sure it is, Sid.
不，这是，希德
It's all... It's all a movie.
所有的... 所有的都是一场电影
It's all...
人生就像...
one great big movie.
一场巨大的电影
Only you can't pick your genre.
只是，你不能选择电影的类型
Why can't I be a Meg Ryan movie?
那我为什么在这场电影中不能 像梅格·瑞恩那样呢？
Or even a good porno.
或者，甚至出演一个高级脱星？
What?
什么？
You heard me.
你听到了
Are you sure?
真的吗？
Yeah.
是的
I think so.
是真的
Look, look, look. Here it comes.
注意，注意，注意， 快到了
- Whoa! - Ohh!
- 哇！ - 哦！
The blood is all wrong!
那上面的血太不真实了！
Why do they do that? It's too red!
他们为什么用那个？太红了！
Wait. Here comes another.
等等，另一个快到了
- Oooh! Oooh! - Yes! Yes!
- 哇！哇！ - 好！好！
Predictable. I knew he was gonna bite it.
太俗套了， 我早知道他要杀人
How can you watch this shit over and over?
你们怎么能忍受一遍又一遍 地看这种垃圾呢？
Shh!
嘘！
I wanna see Jamie Lee's breasts.
我想看杰米·李的波波
When do we see Jamie Lee's breasts?
我们什么时侯才能看到 杰米·李的波波？
Breasts?
波波？
Not until "Trading Places" in '83.
直到83年的《交易场》才能看得到
Jamie Lee was always the virgin in horror movies.
杰米·李在恐怖电影中一直扮的是处女，
She never showed her tits 'til she went legits.
直到改演正统戏时才露出胸部
Could afford a decent pair.
她那对长得又不好看
That's why she always outsmarted the killer in the big chase scene at the end.
这就是她最后的大追逐中总是 能够智胜杀手缘故
Only virgins can do that. Don't you know the rules?
只有处女才能这样 你们知道这些规则吗？
- What rules? - You don't...
- 哪些规则？ - 你不知道...
Jesus Christ. You don't know the rules?
天哪！ 你不知道这些规则？
Have an aneurysm, why don't ya?
有毛病艾我们为什么要知道？
There are certain rules one must abide by...
只有遵守几个必要的规则...
in order to successfully survive a horror movie.
一个人才能在恐怖电影中最后活下来
For instance, number one: You can never have sex.
例如，规则一： 不能做爱
Big no-no! Big no-no!
别！别这样！
l'd be a dead man.
那我肯定会死的
Sex equals death. Okay?
做爱就等于死亡，知道不？
Number two: You can never drink or do drugs.
规则二： 不能喝酒和吸毒
No, the sin factor.
其实，是罪恶因素在起作用
It's a sin. It's an extension of number one.
喝酒吸毒是一种罪行 这也是规则一的扩展
And number three: Never, ever, ever under any circumstances, say...
规则三：在任何情况下， 从不要，绝对不要说...
"I'll be right back",  'cause you won't be back.
“我马上回来”， 因为你不可能回来了
I'm gettin' another beer. You want one?
我再去拿一瓶啤酒去， 你也想要吗？
Yeah, sure.
好的，当然
- I'll be right back! - Ohhhh!
- 我马上回来！ - 噢!
You push the laws and you end up dead.
你不遵守规则，最后肯定会死
See you in the kitchen with a knife.
好吧，我等会儿到厨房里去看你 插着刀子的尸体
Only virgins can outsmart the killer in the big chase scene at the end.
只有处女才能在最后的大追逐中 智胜杀手
- Don't you know the rules? - What rules?
- 你们知道这些规则吗？ - 哪些规则？
You don't know the rules?
你不知道这些规则？
There are rules one must abide by to survive a horror movie.
只有遵守几个必要的规则， 才能在电影中活下来
Boring.
无聊
For instance
例如
The sheriff just radioed.
治安官刚刚无线电通知我，
Somebody reported a car in the bushes down the road.
有人报告说在这条路边的灌木丛里发现了一辆车
I'm gonna go check it out.
我准备去查看一下
- Would you care to join me? - I'd love to.
- 愿意跟我一起去吗？ - 很愿意
If you're sure it's all right.
如果你确信不会出问题的话
Uh, ma'am, I'm the deputy of this town.
唉，女士， 我是这个镇上的副警长呀！
Be right back.
马上回来
You push the laws, you end up dead.
你不遵守规则， 最后肯定会死
- W... Excuse me, ma'am. - Mm-hmm?
- 哦... 对不起，女士 - 嗯？
I thought maybe we'd walk.
我想我们可以走过去
It's such a nice night out. I got a flashlight.
今天晚上外面天气真好 我有手电
You're not scared, are ya?
你没有害怕吧，对吗？
No.
没有
- All right. - Great.
- 走吧 - 太好了
- Do you know what that constellation is? - No. What is it?
- 你知道那是什么星座吗？ - 不知道那是什么？
I don't know. That's why I was askin' you
我也不知道，所以才问你
What happened to Tatum, Stu?
塔特姆怎么了，斯图？
She probably got pissed at me and bailed. Bye.
她可能是生我气了，不知道跑哪儿 去了再见
No, I'm just kidding.
没事，我只是开个玩笑
Look! Here comes the obligatory tit shot!
快看！必须有的波波秀来了
- Yes! Oh! Beautiful! - Lovely!
- 好！噢！太美了！ - 真可爱！
Ohh! Ohh.
哦！哦！
- Oh, my God. - I'll leave you guys alone.
- 哦，天哪！ - 你们慢慢看，我走了
You are so...
你真是...
amazing.
令人惊叹
Hello? Yeah?
喂？什么？
Holy shit.
哦，老天哪！
Listen up.
听着
They found Principal Himbry dead.
他们发现校长希伯瑞死了
- Hey. Hey. - To arms! To arms!
- 嗨！嗨！ - 去看校长！去看校长！
- Where did he say he was? - At the football field!
- 他说他在哪儿？ - 在橄榄球场
- Come on! - Where you guys goin'?
- 快走！ - 你们都要去哪儿？
We were just gettin' to the good part.
快到最精彩的部分了
Hello? Yeah?
喂？什么？
Whoo!
哇！
Hi-ho, Silver! Let's go!
哈-嗬, 让我们出发！
So, is... is Dewey your real name?
那，杜...杜威是你的真名吗？
No, it's Dwight.
不，真名是德怀特
Dwight?
德怀特？
- I'm sorry. - No, that's all right.
- 对不起 - 不，没关系
Dewey's just somethin' I got stuck with a long time ago.
只是人们叫我杜威已经很长时间了
Well, I like it.
我喜欢这个名字
Sexy.
很性感
- Sexy? - Mm-hmm.
- 性感？ - 嗯...哼
Ah, it's just this town's way of not takin' me serious.
呵，这个镇上的人并没有把我当回事
What about Gale Weathers?
那他们是如何对基尔·唯茨的呢？
Sounds like I'm a meteorologist or something.
我这名字听起来就像气象学家之类的 什么东西一样
People treat me...
人们对我...
like I'm the antichrist of television journalism.
就像我是电视新闻业里的老鼠屎一样
- I don't think you're that bad. - No?
- 我认为你并没有那么坏 - 没有？
- No? - No.
- 没有？ - 没有
That's just 'cause you kinda like me.
那只是因为你有些喜欢我而已
They sure are comin' fast. Slow down!
他们真是开得太快了慢点！
Freeze... Jump!
别动... 跳！
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
对不起，你没事吧？
Yeah.
没有
I'm sorry.
对不起
I'm on duty.
我正执行公务
Is that what you're looking for?
那是你正在找的吗？
My whole life.
我一生中都在
- Damn! - What?
- 该死！ - 什么？
- What is it? - This is Neil Prescott's car.
- 怎么了？ - 这是尼尔·普里斯科特的汽车
- Sidney's father? - Yeah.
- 希德内的父亲？ - 对
Jesus. What's he doing here?
老天，他来这儿干什么？
We gotta get back.
我们快回去
You okay?
你没事吧？
Yeah.
当然
Yeah, I'm fine
没事，我很好
Who'd you call?
你打给谁了？
What?
什么？
Um, well, I don't know, when you're arrested you're allowed one phone call.
嗯，没什么当你被捕时，你 可以允许打一个电话
So I was just curious. Who'd you call?
我只是很好奇，你打给谁了？
Called my dad.
打给我爸了
No, um, Sheriff Burke called your dad. I saw him.
不会吧，嗯，治安官伯克打给他的 我看见了
Yeah, but when I called I didn't get an answer.
当然是，不过我打的时候，没人接
Huh.
哼！
You don't still think it was me, do ya?
你不会还认为是我吧，是不是？
No.
没有
I was just thinking,
我只是在想
if it were you it'd be a very clever way to throw me off track.
如果真是你的话，有一 个非常聪明的办法可以骗住我
You know, using your one phone call to call me so I wouldn't think it was you.
你知道，如果你当时打电话给我， 我就不会认为是你
Really.
真的？
What do I have to do to prove to you that I'm not a killer?
我该怎么做才能使你相信我不是凶手？
- Oh, my God. - Huh?
- 哎呀，天哪！ - 翱
- Oh, my God. - Sidney - Billy, watch out!
- 哎呀，天哪！ - 希德内 - 比利，注意！
- Aaah! - Aaaah!
- 啊 - 啊...！
Sid.
希德
Shit!
糟了！
Help me, somebody! Help me!
救命！有人吗？救命！
Help me!
救命啦！
No, Jamie. Uh, watch out.
不，杰米 艾注意
Watch out, Jamie. You know he's around.
注意，杰米 你知道他在附近
You... You know...
你...你知道的...
Look, there he is. I told you.
注意，他来了 我告诉过你了
I told you he was right around the corner.
我告诉过你他就在那个角落里
Jamie. Jamie.
杰米，杰米
Jamie, look behind you. Look behind you.
杰米，注意身后 注意身后
Turn around. Behind you.
转身 在你后面
All the time! Behind you!
一直都在你后面！
Behind you, Jamie.
你身后，杰米
Jamie, turn around. Ohh! God! Yeah.
杰米，转身 噢！天哪！
Help me! Help!
救命！救命！
Let me in!
让我进去！
- The killer's coming after me! He's in the house! - Where? Wait.
- 杀手在追我！他在屋子里！ - 哪儿？等等
- There's a camera in the house. Look. - Behind you!
- 屋子里有一个摄像机，你看 - 在你身后！
- Oh, my God. No. - Oh, shit.
- 噢，天哪不 - 噢，糟糕
Jamie. Jamie.
杰米，杰米
- Behind you, kid! - Randy!
- 你后面，孩子！ - 兰迪！
- Behind ya! -  Look around!
- 你身后！ -  往后看！
- Shit. - What?
- 糟糕 - 什么？
- We're on 30-second delay. - Oh, my God.
- 我们有30秒的延时 - 噢，天哪
Aaaah!
啊...！
The... door.
门...门
Aaah!
啊
- Is there a phone in the van? - Yeah.
- 你的车里有电话吗？ - 有
Lock yourself in it. Call the sheriff for backup.
把自己锁在里面 快叫治安官来支援
Be careful!
小心点！
Neil?
尼尔？
Mr. Prescott?
普里斯科特先生？
Shit!
靠！
Oh!
噢！
Kenny, I need the cellular!
肯尼，我需要手机！
Kenny!
肯尼！
- Kenny! -  Kenny! Kenny!
- 肯尼！ -  肯尼！肯尼！
9-1-1.
9-1-1
- What's going on?   - Ooh! Aah!
- 怎么了？  - 嚯！啊
Aaaah!
啊...！
Oh, God!
噢，天哪！
Oh!
啊
Stop!
停！
Oh, God!
艾天哪！
Dewey!
杜威！
Dewey, where are you?
杜威，你在哪儿？
Dewey!
杜威1
Sidney?
希德内？
Dewey!
杜威！
Shit!
糟糕！
7825, suspect at 105 North Avenue 52.
7825，嫌疑犯在北52街105号
Hello. Help me, please. I'm at Stu Marker's house on Turner Lane.
喂请快救我我在特纳道上的 斯图·马克家
It's 261 Turner Lane. Please, he's going to try and kill me.
这里是特纳道261号 请快点，他想杀我
Sidney! Sidney!
希德内！希德内！
Jesus, we've got to get the fuck out of here!
天哪，我们快离开这个鬼地方吧！
Stop right there!
停那儿别动！
Don't shoot. It's me! I found Tatum. She's dead.
别开枪，是我！ 我找到了塔特姆，她死了
- I think Stu did it. - Don't listen to him, Sidney!
- 我认为是斯图干的 - 别听他的，希德内！
- Stay back! - Stu did it.
- 别过来！ - 斯图干的
- He killed Billy. He killed my Tatum.  - You did it!
- 他杀了比利他杀了我的塔特姆  - 是你杀的！
- He killed my Tatum!  - No, I didn't!
- 他杀了我的塔特姆！  - 不，我没有！
You lie!
你撒谎！
He killed my Tatum!
他杀了我的塔特姆！
- No, I didn't! - You lie!
- 不，我没有！ - 你撒谎！
Sidney, baby, please, give me that gun!
希德内，乖乖，请把枪给我！
Give me that gun! Christ, man!
把枪给我！老天！
No, I didn't. Sid, he did it!
不，不是我 希德，是他杀的
He did it, Sidney! Please, I didn't do it.
他杀的，希德内！请相信， 不是我杀的
He did it. Please!
是他杀的，相信我！
- Please, Sidney. Oh! - Fuck you both!
- 请相信我，希德内噢！ - 滚你们俩儿的蛋！
- Please! - No! No! Sidney!
- 请别！ - 不！不！希德内！
Open up! He did it!
开门！是他干的！
Help me! He's going crazy!
快救我！他疯了！
- Sidney! - Go away!
- 希德内！ - 滚！
Sidney?
希德内？
Leave me alone
都给我走开
- Sid. - Billy.
- 希德 - 比利
Oh! Billy. Billy. Are you okay?
噢！比利，比利 你没事儿吧？
- I'm okay. - I thought you were dead.
- 我没事 - 我还以为你死了
No, I'm like a stuck pig, but I'm all right.
没有，虽然象一头中了镖的野猪， 但是我没事
Get up.
起来
- I'm okay. - You're bleeding.
- 我没事 - 你在流血
- Oh, my God. - We've gotta get help.
- 噢，天哪 - 我们需要帮助
No, he's out there!
不，他在外面！
No, give me the gun. Give me the gun. It's okay.
不，把枪给我，把枪给我， 没问题的
It's okay. It's okay.
没问题，没问题
Careful.
小心
- Please help me! - Come in, come in!
- 请救救我！ - 进来，进来！
Stu's flipped out! He's gone mad!
斯图精神错乱了！ 他发疯了！
We all go a little mad sometimes.
每个人有时候都会发点儿疯的
- No, Billy! - Oh, fuck!
- 不，比利！ - 噢，他妈的！
Anthony Perkins, "Psycho."
安东尼·帕金斯的《惊魂记》
Mmm.
哦
Corn syrup. Same stuff they used for pig's blood in "Carrie."
玉米糖浆在《凶灵》中就是用的 这个来替代猪血的
Stu.
斯图
Help me, please.
请救救我
Surprise, Sidney.
惊诧吧，希德内
- No! - Ooh!
- 不！ - 哦！
Oh, now. Whoa.
哦，可以了，哇
What's the matter, Sidney? You look like you've seen a ghost.
怎么啦，希德内？ 你看起来就像是见到鬼了
Why are you doing this?
你们为什么要这样做？
It's all part of the game, Sidney.
所有这些只是一个游戏而已，希德内
It's called "Guess How I'm Gonna Die."
名字叫做“猜猜看，我会怎么死”
Fuck you!
去你妈的！
No, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不
We already played that game, remember?
我们已经玩过这个游戏了，还记得吗？
- You lost. - It's a fun game, Sidney.
- 你失败了 - 这是个有趣的游戏，希德内
See, we ask you a question, and if you get it wrong,
知道吗？我们问你一个问题， 如果你答错了,
"boo-kah", you die!
“砰...咔”，你死了！
You get it right, you die.
要是答对了，你也死
You're crazy, both of you.
你们两个全疯了
Actually, we prefer the term "psychotic."
事实上，我们更喜欢用“精神病” 这个词
- You'll never get away with this. - Oh, no?
- 你们逃不了的 - 哦，不会吗？
Tell that to Cotton Weary.
你应该对科顿·威而瑞说这话
You wouldn't believe how easy he was to frame.
你简直想不到嫁祸给他是多么容易
Watch a few movies, take a few notes.
看几场电影，记下些电影里的手段
- It was fun.  - No!
- 真是很有趣呀 - 不！
- Whoa! - Where're you goin'?
- 喂！ - 你想要去哪儿呀？
Why?
为什么？
Why did you kill my mother?
你们为什么杀死我妈？
Why? Why?
为什么？为什么？
Did you hear that, Stu? I think she wants a motive.
你听到了吗，斯图？ 她想要我的动机
I don't really believe in motive, Sid.
我真的是不相信什么动机之说的， 希德
I mean, did Norman Bates have a motive?
我的意思是，你知道诺曼·贝茨 有动机吗？
No.
没有
Did they ever really decide why Hannibal Lecter liked to eat people?
那他们真的知道汉尼拔·莱克特为什么爱吃人肉吗？
Don't think so!
他们不知道！
See, it's a lot scarier when there's no motive, Sid.
所以，如果没有动机，那就更恐怖， 希德
We did your mom a favor, Sid.
我们是在帮你老娘，希德
That woman was a slut-bag whore
那个女人就是一个毫不知耻的荡妇
who flashed her shit all over town like she was Sharon Stone.
在我们镇上四处找人上她，当自己是莎朗·斯通似的
Yeah, we put her out of her misery,
是艾我们把她从不幸中解脱出来了
cause let's face it, Sidney,
因为让我们直说吧，希德内
your mother was no Sharon Stone, hmm?
你老娘不是莎朗·斯通，嗯？
Is that motive enough for you?
你说那个动机够了吗？
How about this?
那这个呢？
Your slut mother was fucking my father,
你那母狗老娘曾操过我爸，
and she's the reason my mom moved out and abandoned me.
就是她，使得我妈出走，抛弃了我
How's that for a motive?
这个动机怎么样？
Maternal abandonment causes serious deviant behavior.
没有母爱的孩子会产生严重的变态 行为
lt certainly fucked you up.
这已经在你身上验证了
lt made you have sex with a psychopath.
它使得你刚才竟和一个精神病发生 性关系
That's right. You gave it up. Now you're no longer a virgin. Oooh!
太对了你放弃了 现在你已经不是一个处女了，哇！
I said "virgin". Whoops!
我说的是“处女”，哦...哇！
Now you gotta die. Those are the rules.
现在你要死了 这是规则
Let's pretend it's all a scary movie, Sid.
让我们假装所有这些只是一个恐怖影片
How do you think it's gonna end?
希德你说这结局会是怎样的？
Oh! Oh! This is the greatest part! You're gonna love this.
哦！哦！这是最精彩的部分！ 你一定会喜欢这个的
We got a surprise for you, Sidney.
我们要给你一个惊奇，希德
Yeah, you're gonna love this one.
是艾你一定会喜欢这个的
It's a scream, baby!
这就是“惊声尖叫”，宝贝！
Hold on a sec. I'll be right back.
等一会儿，我马上回来
You know what time it is, Sid?
你知道现在是什么时侯吗，希德？
It's after midnight.
现在刚过午夜
It's your mom's anniversary. Congratulations.
是你妈死去的周年，祝贺你
We killed her exactly one year ago today.
我们正好在一年前的今天杀了她
Attention! Oh, what do we have behind door number three, Sidney?
注意了！哦，三号门后面有什么来着， 希德内？
- Daddy! - Whoa, hold it.
- 爸爸！ - 噢，别动
That's enough.
够了
- Guess we won't be needing this anymore. - Uh-huh!
- 看起来我们不再需要这个了 - 是啊
And, oh, look at this. Ring, ring. Won't need this.
还有，哦，看看这个 叮铃铃，叮铃铃，也不需要了
Got the ending figured out yet, Sid?
最后明白了吧，希德？
Come on, Sidney. You think about it now, huh?
来吧，希德内 你想想看，嗯？
Your daddy's the chief suspect. We cloned his cellular.
你老爹是头号嫌疑犯 我们复制了他的手机
The evidence is all right there, baby!
所有的证据都在这儿，宝贝
What if your father snapped?
如果你老爹最终忍受不了了，会 发生什么事？
Your mother's anniversary set him off,
你妈死去的周年，诱发了你老爹的狂性
and he went on a murder spree, killing everyone.
他于是来了个屠杀纵乐，杀 光了所有的人
Except for Billy and me. We were left for dead.
当然除了比利和我 我俩被认为死了而逃脱了他的魔掌
Then he... kills you...
然后他...杀死了你...
and shoots himself in the head.
再往自己头上开了一枪
- Perfect ending. - I thought of that.
- 完美的结局 - 这是我想到的
Watch this.
看这个
- Ready? - Yeah. Yeah! I'm ready, baby!
- 好了吗？ - 是，是的！我准备好了，宝贝！
Right! Get up! Yeah, babe, get up! Hit it!
对！快来！ 是艾宝贝，快来！快刺！
Good one, man. Jesus.
不错，哥儿们，天哪
Oh, shit.
噢，天哪
My turn.
该我了
Don't forget. Stay to the side and don't go too deep.
别忘了，不要太正，也不要太深
Okay. I'll remember.
好的，记住了
Aaah! Fuck! Fuck!
啊他妈的！他妈的！
Fuck! Goddamn it, Stu!
他妈的！你他妈的！斯图！
Sorry, Billy. I guess I got a little too zealous, huh?
对不起，比利我猜我只是太有点 热心帮你了，嗯？
- Give me the knife. - No.
- 把刀给我 - 不
Give me the knife!
把刀给我
Now!
快！
You see, Sid, everybody dies but us.
你看，希德，除了我和比利
Everybody dies but us.
所有人都死了除了我们所有人都死了
We get to carry on and plan the sequel,
我们还要继续下去，还要计划续集，
'cause let's face it, baby, these days ya gotta have a sequel!
你知道吗，宝贝？现在的年代， 续集是必不可少的！
You sick fucks. You've seen one too many movies.
你们这两个变态杂种 你们看了太多的电影了
Now, Sid, don't you blame the movies.
听着，希德，你还敢归咎于电影？
I feel a little woozy here!
我这儿已经感到很晕了
Movies don't create psychos.
电影根本不制造精神变态的人，
All right. All right, you get the gun.
好吧，好吧 你拿着枪
I'll untie Pops, okay?
我来把这个家伙解开，好吗？
- Now! - Okay.
- 快点！ - 是
Um. Uh...
呃...嗯...
Houston, we... we have a problem here.
我们... 我们有麻烦了
- What? - The gun, man. The gun.
- 怎么了？ - 枪，哥们儿那把枪
I put it right there, and it's not there.
我刚才就放在这儿的， 现在它不见了
- Where the fuck is it? - Right here, asshole.
- 他妈的，跑哪儿去了？ - 在这儿，混蛋
Man, I thought she was dead.
老兄，我以为她已经死了
She looked dead, man.
她刚才看起来是像死了，老兄
- Still does. - I've got an ending for you.
- 现在还一样 - 我来给你们一个结局
The reporter left for dead in the news van
那个记者因为看起来像死了，所以杀手放过了她
comes to,
她醒后，
stumbles on you two dipshits,
发现了真凶是你们两个笨蛋，
finds the gun,
她找到了枪，
foils your plan and saves the day.
阻止了你们两个的阴谋，扭转了败局
I like that ending.
我喜欢这个结局
I know something you don't.
我知道一些你不知道的事情
Fuck. No!
混蛋，不！
Yeah, man.
好，哥儿们
Yeah. Aw, so sweet.
好噢，太可爱了
It works better without the safety on.
拉开了枪栓，这个才能起作用
This is Gale Weathers signing off.
这是基尔·唯茨，播送到此结束
Babe, you're gonna love this!
宝贝，你会喜欢这个的！
Shit.
他妈的
What?
什么？
Where are they? Where are they?
他们跑哪儿去了？ 他们跑哪儿去了？
I don't know, but I'm hurtin', man.
我不知道， 我伤得很重，哥儿们
Fuck!
我靠！
Shall I let the machine get it?
要不要等留言机接？
- Hello? -  Are you alone in the house?
- 喂？ -  你一个人在家吗？
Bitch! You bitch! Where the fuck are you?
婊子！你这个婊子！ 你他妈的在哪儿？
Not so fast. We're gonna play a little game.
不远 我们来玩一个小游戏吧
It's called "Guess Who Just Called The Police And
名叫“猜猜看是谁向警察报告了你们
Reported Your Sorry Motherfucking Ass."
这两个可怜的、不要脸的蠢驴”
Find her, you dipshit. Get up.
找到她，你这个笨蛋起来
I can't, Billy. You cut me too deep.
我不行了，比利你刺得太深了
I think I'm dying here, man.
我猜我会死在这儿，哥儿们
Talk to her. Talk to her.
跟她讲话，跟她讲话
Hello.
喂
Oh, Stu, Stu, Stu. What's your motive?
哦，斯图艾斯图，斯图你的动机是什么呀？
Billy's got one. The police are on their way.
比利已有一个了警察就要来了
What are you gonna tell them?
等会儿你会怎么告诉他们呢？
Peer pressure. I'm far too sensitive.
纯粹是压力 我太过于敏感了
I'm gonna rip you up, you bitch,
我要把你撕成碎片，你这个婊子
just like your fucking mother!
让你像你他妈的老娘一样！
You've gotta find me first, you pansy-assed mama's boy!
那你要先找到我才行艾你这个 杂种！
Fuck!
我靠！
Ow. You fuckin' hit me with the phone, dick!
唉，你他妈的用电话打我，你个吊
Fucker, where are you?
婊子，你在哪儿？
You fuck!
你这个婊子
Did you really call the police?
你真给警察打电话了？
You bet your sorry ass I did.
当然，你这个可怜的蠢猪
My mom and dad are gonna be so mad at me.
我爸妈会为我疯掉的
Aaah! Bitch!
啊婊子！
Aaah!
啊
Aah!
Ohh! My arm!
嗷！我的胳膊！
I always had a thing for ya, Sid!
我一直对你有好感呢，希德！
Bitch.
婊子
I'm sorry. It's all right.
对不起没事了
Oh, my God, Randy, I thought you were dead.
噢，天哪，兰迪， 我还以为你死了
I probably should be.
我可能本来该死，可我是处男
I never thought I'd be so happy to be a virgin.
从没想到自己会为此而这么高兴
Fucker!
婊子！
Say hello to your mother.
去向你妈问好吧
Aaah!
啊
It's okay.
没事了
Guess I remembered the safety that time, you bastard.
这次应该没忘记打开保险了吧， 你这个杂种
Careful.
小心
This is the moment when the supposedly dead killer comes back to life...
这是本来应该死了的杀手再次复活的时刻...
for one last scare.
最后一次惊吓
Not in my movie.
在我的电影中没有
Dad.
爸爸
Randy, help me out.
兰迪，帮帮我
- Ow. Aah. - Are you okay?
- 嗷，啊 - 你没事吧？
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
- 你没事吧？ - 没事
- Hang in there, buddy. - All right.
- 放在那儿，伙计们 - 好的
- Over here. - Sorry, kid.
- 这儿 - 对不起，孩子
Okay, I think it's going to go something like this. Just stay with me.
好了，我想这样就可以了，注意跟着我
Hi, this is Gale Weathers...
大家好，这是基尔·唯茨...
with an exclusive eyewitness account of this amazing breaking story.
独家现场报道这起惊人的爆炸性新闻
Several more local teens are dead...
几个更多的本地青少年死了...
bringing to an end the harrowing mystery of the mass killing
结束了这起残忍的多重谋杀案，并揭开了其神秘的真相
that has terrified this peaceful community...
这起事件使这个安静的小镇笼罩在恐惧之中...
like the plot of some scary movie.
就像是一些恐怖电影里的情节
lt all began with a scream over 9-1-1...
事件从打给9-1-1电话里的尖叫声开始...
and ended in a bloodbath that has rocked the town of Woodsboro,
到这场震惊了伍兹士堡小镇的血腥 屠杀结束
all played out here in this peaceful farmhouse...
屠杀发生在这个平静的农舍里...
far from the crimes and the sirens of the larger cities...
这里远离大城市的犯罪和警笛声...
that its residents had fled.
是那儿的人们向往的地方
Okay, let's take it back to one. Come on. Move it.
好了，把它拿回去快，快走
This is my big shot. Let's go.
这是我的大制作让我们走